and we're recording it's like a great just remind you again
우리는 좋은처럼 기록 단지 당신을 다시 생각 나게하는
hello recording the closest so if you're uncomfortable speaking on camera here
당신이 카메라에 불편 말하기를하는 경우, 그래서 안녕하세요 가장 가까운 기록
not in the picture but your voice might be on the recording ok great as you can
아니 그림에 있지만 음성은 당신이 수 확인 위대한 기록에있을 수 있습니다
see also the screen is wider than it should be and I'm not sure how to fix it
참조 또한 화면은해야보다 넓은 내가 그것을 해결하는 방법을 잘 모르겠어요
so hard to live with it
함께 사는 열심히
likely your visual cortex is very good and very invariance to stretching so
가능성이 시각 피질 그래서 스트레칭에 아주 좋은 아주 불변이다
this is not a problem
이것은 문제가되지 않는다
ok so what's up with some administrative things before we dive into the class the
우리는 클래스로 다이빙을하기 전에 확인 그래서 일부 관리 것들로까지 무엇이야
first assignment will come out tonight or early tomorrow it is you in january
첫 임무는 월을하다 오늘 밤 또는 이른 내일 나올 것입니다
20 have exactly two weeks you will be writing a classifier earlier classifier
20 정확히 2 주 당신이 분류 이전 분류를 작성하는 것이
and a small two-layer neural network you'll be writing the entirety of
작은 두 계층 신경망 당신의 전체를 작성 할 수 있습니다
backpropagation algorithm for 22 layer neural network will cover all that
22 층 신경 네트워크의 역 전파 알고리즘을 모두 충당 할 수
material in next two weeks and morning by the way there are some in from last
2 주 아침에 재료에 의해 일부는 마지막에서가
year as well and we're changing the assignments so they will please do not
그들이하지 기쁘게 있도록 올해도 우리는 할당을 변경하고
complete in 2015 assignment that's something to be aware of and for your
과에 대한주의해야 할 뭔가 2,015 할당에 완료하여
competition but it will be using Python and pie and will also be offering
경쟁은하지만 파이썬과 파이를 사용하는 것 또한 제공됩니다
terminal dot com which is which is basically the virtual machines in the
에서 기본적으로 가상 머신 인 것입니다 터미널 닷컴
club that you can use if you don't have a very good laptop and so on
당신이 그렇게에 아주 좋은 노트북을 가지고하지 않을 경우 사용할 수있는 클럽
go into detail about it but i just like to point out that for the first
그것에 대해 세부 사항으로 이동하지만 난 그냥 제에 대한 것을 지적하고자
assignment we assume that you'll be relatively familiar with Python you'll
할당 우리는 당신이거야 파이썬 비교적 잘 알고있을거야 가정
be writing these optimized numpy expressions where you at manipulating
어디 조작에이 최적화 된 NumPy와 식을 작성한다
these matrices and vectors and very efficient forms so for example if you're
이 행렬과 벡터 예를 들어 당신이 있다면, 그래서 매우 효율적인 형태
seeing this code and its doesn't mean anything to you then please have a look
이 코드를보고 그 다음 당신에게 아무것도 의미하지 않는 것은 봐주세요
at our python tutorial that is up on the website as well it's written by Justin
이 저스틴에 의해 작성된 것뿐만 아니라 웹 사이트에 가입 우리의 파이썬 튜토리얼에서
and is very good and so go through that and familiarize yourself with the
매우 좋은이며, 그래서 통과하고 익숙해
notation because you'll be seeing you writing a lot of code that looks like
표기법 당신과 같은 코드를 많이 작성을 볼 수있을 것이기 때문에
this where we doing all these optimize operations so they're fast enough to run
그들은 충분히 빨리 실행하는 것, 그래서 우리가하고있는 곳이이 작업을 최적화하는 모든
on the CPU now in terms of total basically what this amounts to is that
CPU에서 지금은 전체의 관점에서이 있다는 것입니다 금액 기본적으로 무엇을
will give you a link to the assignment you'll go to a web page and you'll see
당신에게 할당에 대한 링크를 제공합니다 당신은 웹 페이지로 이동합니다 당신은 볼 수 있습니다
something like this this is a virtual machine in the cloud that has been set
이 같은 일이 설정되어 클라우드에서 가상 머신이다
up with all the dependencies of the assignment they're all installed already
과제의 모든 종속성까지 그들은 모두 이미 설치되어있는
on the data is already there and so you click on lunch machine and this'll
데이터가 이미 존재하고에 그래서 당신은 점심 시스템에서 클릭하고이는거야
basically bring you to something like this this is running your brother and
기본적으로이 이런 일에 당신을 데려 동생을 실행하고
this is basically a thin layer on top of an AWS
이것은 기본적 AWS 위에 얇은 층
machine a UI layer here and so you have an iPod the notebook and a little
기계 여기 그래서 UI 층에는 노트북과 조금 아이팟이
terminal and you can go around and this is just like a machine in the cloud and
터미널 당신은 주위에 갈 수있는이 클라우드에 그냥 기계처럼이며,
so they have some CPU offerings and they also have some GPU machines that you can
그래서 그들은 어떤 CPU 제품을 가지고 그들은 또한 당신이 할 수있는 일부 GPU 시스템을
use and so on
그래서 사용
normally have to pay for terminal but will be distributing credits to you so
일반적으로 단말기 비용을 지불해야하지만, 그래서 당신에게 크레딧을 분배한다
you just lost to a specific ta that will decide in a bit you email to a TA and
당신은 단지 당신이 TA에 이메일을 보내 비트에 결정할 것이다 따 특정 손실과
ask for money will send you money and we keep track of how much money we sent to
돈을 요구하는 것은 당신에게 돈을 보내 우리는 우리가로 전송 얼마나 많은 돈을 추적합니다
all the people so you have to be responsible with the funds so this is
모든 사람들은 그래서 당신은 그래서 이것이 자금과 책임을 가지고
also an option for you to use you like ok any details are you can you can read
또한 옵션은 모든 세부 사항 당신이 읽을 수 수 있습니다 확인처럼 사용하기 위해
it if you like it's not required for your comment
당신은 당신의 의견이 필요하지있어 좋아하는 경우
but you can probably get there around yeah ok sam says that to happen to the
하지만 당신은 아마 주위에서 얻을 수 그래 좋아 샘이 일어날 것을 말한다
lecture now today we'll be talking about which classification and specially will
강의는 이제 오늘 우리가 이야기 할 것입니다있는 분류 및 특수 것
start off on linear classifiers so we talk about the classification the basic
우리는 분류의 기본을 이야기하도록 선형 분류에 시작
task is that we have some number of categories say dog cat truck plane or so
작업은 우리가 범주의 일부 수 있도록 개 고양이 트럭 평면 또는 말을해야한다는 것입니다
on we get to decide what these are and then asked earlier to take an image
우리는 그 다음이 무엇인지를 결정하는 얻을에 이미지를 촬영하기 이전 요청
which is a giant breed of numbers and we have to transform into one of these
어떤 숫자의 거대한 품종이며, 우리는이 중 하나에 변환해야
labels we have to build it into one of the categories this problem will spend
라벨 우리는이 문제가 지출 범주 중 하나에 그것을 구축해야
most of our time talking about this one specifically but if you'd like to do any
우리의 대부분의 시간은 구체적으로이 일에 대해 이야기하지만 당신은 하나를 수행하려는 경우
other task in computer vision such as detection image capture any segmentation
이러한 검출 이미지 캡처 어떤 분할 등의 컴퓨터 비전에서 다른 작업
or whatever else you'll find that once he know about the classification and how
또는 어떤 다른 당신은 찾을 그가 분류 방법에 대해 알고 나면 그
that's done everything else is just the tiny built on top of it so you'll be in
다른이 이루어집니다 모든 그래서 당신이 알 수있을 것입니다 그것의 상단에 내장 단지 작은입니다
a great position to do any of the other tasks so it's really good for conceptual
이 개념에 대한 정말 좋은, 그래서 좋은 위치는 다른 작업을 수행 할 수
understanding and we'll work through that as a specific example to simplify
이해하고 우리는 간단하게 구체적인 예로서 그 통해 작동합니다
things in the beginning now why is this problem hard just give an idea the
처음에 일이 지금 왜이 문제는 하드 그냥 생각를 제공한다
problem is what we refer to as a semantic gap this image here as a giant
문제는 우리가 거​​대한 여기에 의미 론적 차이로이 이미지를 참조 할 것입니다
grid of numbers the way the images are represented in the computer is that this
숫자의 격자 이미지가 컴퓨터에 표시되는 방식이 있다는
is basically say roughly 300 by a hundred by three accelerates oh three
세 오 기본적으로 가속화 세에 의해 약 300 백으로 말
dimensional array and threes from the three color channels red green and blue
적색, 녹색, 청색 세 가지 색상 채널에서 차원 배열과 열로
and so when you zoom in on the part of that image is basically a giant great
그래서 그 이미지의 일부를 확대 할 때 기본적으로 거대한 중대하다
numbers between 0 and 255 so that's what we have to work with these numbers
0에서 255 사이의 숫자 것은 그래서 우리는이 숫자와 함께 일해야 무엇
indicate the amount of brightness and all the three color channels at every
밝기의 양마다 모든 세 개의 컬러 채널을 나타낸다
single position in the image and so the reason that any specification is
단일 이미지의 위치 및 임의의 사양이되도록 이유
difficult
어려운
when you think about what we have to work with decent like millions of
당신은 우리가 수백만처럼 괜찮은 작업해야 것에 대해 생각할 때
numbers of that form and having to classify things like cats it quickly
그 형태의 번호와 가지고는 신속하게 고양이 등을 분류하기
became apparent to the complexity of the task so for example the camera can be
태스크의 복잡성은 명백 해졌다 그래서 예를 들면 카메라가 될 수있다
rotated around this cat and it can be zoomed in and nothing has shifted the
이 고양이를 중심으로 회전하며 확대 할 수 있고, 아무것도를 이동하지 않았다
focal properties and transaxle that camera can do different and think about
초점 속성과 카메라가 다른 수행과에 대해 생각할 수있는 트랜스 액슬
what happens to the brightness values and as great as you actually do all
무슨 일이 밝기 값으로 발생하고 실제로 모든 할만큼 큰
these transformations with a camera will completely ship all the patterns are
카메라와 함께 이러한 변환은 완전히 모든 패턴이 출시 될 예정이다
changing and we can be robust to all of this there are also many other
변경하고 우리는이 모두에 강력한 될 수 있습니다 많은 다른있다
challenges for example charges up illumination here we have a long cat
예를 들어, 요금에 대한 문제는 여기에 조명까지 우리는 긴 고양이가
white cat we actually have two of them but you can see beyond its a one cat is
흰 고양이는 우리가 실제로 그 두 가지를 가지고 있지만 한 고양이가 넘어 당신은 볼 수 있습니다
clearly made it quite a bit and the other is not but you can still recognize
명확하게 그것을 꽤 만든, 다른 하나는 아니지만 여전히 인식 할 수
two cats and so think about again the brightness valleys on the level of the
두 고양이 등의 수준에 대해 다시 밝기 계곡을 생각한다
grid and what happens to them as he changed all the different things and all
그는 모든 다른 모든 것들을 변화와 같이 그리드 무엇을 그들에게 발생
the possible lighting schemes that we can have in the world with to be robust
우리가 세상에서 가질 수있는 가능한 조명 방식은 견고하기
to all that there's issues off the formation many classes lots of strange
모두에게 많은 클래스를 형성 떨어져 이상한 많은 문제가 있음
arrangement of these objects would like to recognize so cast coming very
이러한 개체의 배열은 매우 오는 캐스트 그렇게 인식하고 싶습니다
different poses with the slides when I create them they're quite dry there's a
슬라이드와 다른 포즈 난 그들이 거기에 아주 건조이야을 만들 때
lot of math and science this is the only time I get to have fun so that's what I
즉, 그래서 수학이 과학의 많은 내가 재미를 얻을 수있는 유일한 시간이다 내가
just somehow everything that occurs to be robust to all of these affirmations
이러한 긍정의 모든 강력한으로 발생 그냥 어떻게 든 모든
you can still recognizes the cat and all of these images despite their problems
당신은 여전히​​ 자신의 문제에도 불구하고 고양이이 모든 이미지를 인식 할 수 있습니다
so sometimes we might not see the pelagic but you still recognizes that's
그래서 가끔 우리는 원양가 표시되지 않을 수 있습니다하지만 당신은 여전히​​ 그건 인식
cat the cat behind a water bottle and there's also a cab there inside a couch
고양이 물 한 병 뒤에 고양이 택시는 소파 내부가 또한있다
even though you're seeing just 10 PCs pieces of this class basically there's
도 기본적으로 거기에이 클래스의 10 개 조각을보고있는 것처럼
problems on background clutter so things can blend into the environment we have
배경 혼란에 문제가 일들이 우리가 가지고있는 환경에 혼합 할 수 있습니다
to be reminded that and there's also the intra-class variation so cat actually
그에게 상기시켰다 그래서 고양이 실제로도 내 수준의 변화 거기에있다
there's a huge amount of cats just species and so they can look different
이 고양이 단지 종의 엄청난 양이다 그래서 그들은 다르게 보일 수 있습니다
ways with your boss to all of that so i just like you to appreciate the
나는 그래서 모두에게 당신의 상사와 방법은 감사하는 것처럼
complexity of the task we consider any one of these independently is difficult
우리는 이러한 독립적 중 하나 고려 작업의 복잡성은 어렵다
but when you consider the cross product of all these different things and have
당신이 모든 다른 것들의 크로스 제품을 고려하고 그러나이
to work across all of that it's actually quite amazing that anything works at all
아무것도 전혀 작동하는지 실제로 아주 놀라운 것을 모두에서 작동합니다
in fact not only does it work but it works really really well almost here
사실 그것은 작동하지만 거의 여기 정말 잘 작동 않습니다뿐만 아니라,
accuracy of categories like this and we can do that in a few dozen milliseconds
이 같은 카테고리의 정확성과 우리는 수십 밀리 초 단위로이 작업을 수행 할 수 있습니다
with the current technology and so that's what you learn about this class
그래서 현재의 기술과 함께 그는이 클래스에 대한 자세한 내용은 무엇입니까
classifier look like basically we're taking this through the area we'd like
기본적으로 우리는 우리가하고 싶은 영역을 통해이 복용하고 같은 분류보기
to produce a class label and when i'd like he's noticed that there is no
클래스 레이블을 생성하고 내가 원하는 때 그는 더 있다는 것을 눈치없는거야
obvious way up actually encoding and you'll this of these classifiers right
확실한 방법까지 실제로 인코딩하고 정액이 분류의이 권리
there's no simple algorithm like say you're taking it all good in class early
일찍 클래스에 모두 좋은 복용하는 말처럼 간단한 알고리즘은 없다
computer science curriculum your writing bubble sort or you're writing something
컴퓨터 과학 교육 과정 당신의 쓰기 거품 정렬 또는 당신이 뭔가를 작성하는
else to do any particular task you can intuit all the possible steps and you
당신은 모든 가능한 단계에와 당신을 직관적으로 할 수 있습니다 특정 작업을 수행 할 다른
can enumerate them and lets them and play with it and analyze it but here
그것들을 열거하고이를 수 있습니다 여기에 함께 연주하고 그것을 분석 할 수 있지만,
there's no algorithm for detecting a cat under all these variations are it's
어떤 알고리즘이 모든 변화에서 고양이를 검출 없다 그것의있다
extremely difficult to think about how you actually write that up what is the
는 IS 당신이 실제로을 작성하는 방법에 대해 생각하기가 매우 어렵습니다
sequence of operations you would do an arbitrary image to detect a cat that's
작업의 순서는의 고양이를 감지하는 임의의 이미지를 할 것
not to say that people haven't tried especially early these a computer but
사람들이 시도하지 않은 말을하지 특히​​ 초기이 컴퓨터 만
there were these explicit approaches as I'd like to call them where you think
나는 당신이 생각하는 경우 그들에게 전화하고 싶습니다 이러한 명시 적 접근이 있었다
about okay I can't say is that he would like to meet you look for little ear
내가 말할 수 없습니다에 대한 괜찮 그는 당신이 작은 귀를 찾아 만나고 싶을 것입니다
pieces so what we'll do is we'll detect all the edges UltraISO edges will
우리가 무엇을 할 거 야 그래서 개는 우리가 울트라 iso는 뜻을 가장자리 모든 가장자리를 감지 할 수 있습니다입니다
classify the different traits of edges and their junctions will create you know
가장자리의 서로 다른 특성을 분류하고 그들의 접합 당신이 알고 만듭니다
libraries of the season will try to find their arrangements and if we ever see
우리가 보면 시즌 라이브러리는 자신의 준비를 찾으려고 할 것이다
anything like that will detect the cat we see any particular texture of some
우리는 몇 가지의 특정 질감을 볼 고양이를 검출 할 것 같은 것을
particular frequencies will attack the cat as you can come up with some rules
당신이 어떤 규칙을 가지고 올 수있는 특정 주파수는 고양이를 공격합니다
but the problem is that once I tell you okay I'd like to actually recognize the
하지만 문제는 내가 좋아 말해 일단 내가 사실을 인식하고 싶습니다이다
boat now or a person when you go back to the drawing board and yet to be like ok
보트 지금 또는 당신이 좋아처럼 다시 드로잉 보드에 아직 갈 사람
what makes a boat exactly what the original pages right it's completely
어떤 원본 페이지를 잘 완전히의 정확히 보트를 만든다
scalable approach to to prosecution as the pressure dropping this class and
이 클래스를 삭제 압력으로 기소로 확장 접근과
approach that works much better as the data-driven approach that we like in the
우리가에 원하는 데이터 중심의 접근 방식으로 매우 잘 작동 방식
framework of machine learning and just to point out that in these days actually
기계 학습의 프레임 워크는 단지 지적 것과 실제로 이러한 일
in the early days they did not have the luxury of using data because at this
초기에 그들은이에 데이터 때문에 사용의 사치를하지 않았다
point in time you're taking your grayscale images of very low resolution
포인트는 시간에 당신은 매우 낮은 해상도의 당신의 그레이 스케일 이미지를 가지고있어
images in your trying to recognize things it's obviously not going to work
당신이 분명히 작동하지 않을거야 것을 인식하려고의 이미지
but with the availability of Internet huge amount of data I can search for
하지만 데이터의 인터넷 엄청난 양의 가용성과 나는를 검색 할 수 있습니다
example for cat on Google and I get lots of cats everywhere and we know that
Google에서 고양이 예를 들어 나는 모든 곳에서 고양이를 많이 얻고 우리는 알고
these are cats based on the surrounding text in the web pages so there's a lot
거기에 많은 그래서 이러한 웹 페이지에서 주변 텍스트를 기반으로 고양이입니다
of data so the way that this now looks like is that we have a training face
데이터의 방식 때문에 지금처럼 보이는이 우리가 훈련 얼굴을 가지고 있다는 것을
where you give me lots of training samples cast
당신은 내게 캐스팅 훈련 샘플을 많이주는 곳
and you tell me about their cats you give me lots of examples of any type of
당신은 자신의 고양이에 대해 말해 당신은 내게 모든 유형의 예를 많이 제공
other category you're interested in
관심있는 다른 카테고리
I do I go away and I trained to model a model is a class and I can then use that
나는 멀리 가야합니까 나는 모델은 클래스 모델 훈련 나는 그 것을 사용할 수 있습니다
model to actually classified data so what i'm given a new image I can look at
모델은 실제로 내가 볼 수있는 새로운 이미지를 부여하고있어 그래서 데이터를 분류합니다
my training data and I can do something with this based on just a pattern
내 훈련 데이터와 난 그냥 패턴에 따라이 함께 뭔가를 할 수
matching and statistics or someone so as a simple example will work within this
매칭 및 통계 또는 간단한 예를 들어이 내에서 작동 할 수 있도록 사람
framework consider the nearest neighbor classifier the way you're single
프레임 워크는 가장 가까운 이웃 분류 당신이 하나있어 방법을 고려
classifier works is that effectively were given destroyed Trade Center will
분류는 효과적으로 파괴 주어진 무역 센터는 것입니다 작동
do a training time as well just remember all the training data so have all the
뿐만 아니라 교육 시간을 그냥 모든 훈련 데이터 그래서 모두가 기억
training data just got here and I remember it now when you give me a test
훈련 데이터는 여기에 도착하고 당신이 나에게 테스트를 줄 때 나는 지금 그것을 기억
image what we'll do is we'll compare the test image to every single one of the
우리가 무엇을 할 거 야 이미지는 우리의 모든 하나 하나에 테스트 이미지를 비교하는 것입니다
images we saw in a train data and we'll just transfer the label over so I'll
이미지는 우리가 기차 데이터를보고 우리는 단지 내가 거를 통해 라벨을 전송합니다
just look through all the images will work with specific case as I go through
그냥 통과로 특정 경우에 작동합니다 모든 이미지를 봐
this I like to be as complete as possible so we'll work with a specific
나는 가능한 한 완전 좋아이 그래서 우리는 특정 도와 드리겠습니다
case of something called Seifert India set the scene for today as it has 10
이 10가로 페르 인도라는 무언가의 경우는 오늘 장면을 설정
labels labels there are 50,000 training images that you have access to and then
라벨은 다음에 액세스 할 수 50,000 훈련 이미지가 레이블
there's a test set of 10 10,000 images where we're going to evaluate how well
우리가 잘하는 방법을 평가하는거야 10 만 이미지의 테스트 세트가있다
the classifiers working and these images are quite tiny they're just little to a
분류기는 작업과 이러한 이미지는 그들이에 그냥 좀있어 아주 작은 있습니다
dataset of 32 by 32 little thumbnail images so the wait nearest neighbor
32 작은 썸네일 이미지로 (32)의 데이터 세트 대기 가까운 이웃 그래서
classifier would work as we take all this training did others given to us
우리는 다른 사람들이 우리에게 주어진 한 모든 교육을로 분류가 작동합니다
fifty thousand just not just i'm suppose we have these ten different examples
오만은 그냥 나는 우리가이 10 개의 다른 사례가 있다고 가정 아니에요
here is our test images along the first call in here what we'll do is we'll look
여기에 우리가 볼 것입니다 무엇을 할 거 야 여기에서 첫 번째 호출을 따라 우리의 테스트 이미지입니다
up the nearest neighbors in the training set of things that are most similar to
가장 유사한 사물의 트레이닝 세트의 가장 가까운 이웃까지
every one of those in just independently so there you see a ranked list of images
다만 독립적 그래서 거기에 그 모든 일이 당신은 이미지의 순위 목록을 보려면
that are most similar to into training data to any one of those 10 to every one
모든 사람에게 그 (10)의 어느 하나에 트레이닝 데이터에 가장 유사하다고
of those test images over there so in the first row will see that there's a
저기 그 테스트 이미지의 첫 번째 행 있도록이 있다고 볼 수 있습니다
truck i think is a test image and there's quite a few images that look
내가 생각하는 트럭은 테스트 이미지와 보면 대부분의 이미지가있다
similar to it will see how exactly where to find similar teeny bit but you can
여기서 비슷한 조그마한 비트를 찾을 당신이 할 수있는 방법을 정확하게 볼 수 그것과 유사
see that the first retreat result is in fact a horse not a truck and that's
첫 번째 후퇴의 결과가 실제로 말을하지 트럭이고, 그건 볼
because of just the arrangement of the blue sky that was thrown off so you can
때문에 당신이 할 수 있도록 던져진 된 푸른 하늘의 단지 배치
see that this will not probably work very well how do we define this is
이것은 아마 우리가이 정의 어떻게 잘 작동하지 않습니다 참조
measured how do we actually do the comparison there are several ways one of
우리가 실제로 비교를 어떻게 측정 여러 가지 방법 중 하나가 있습니다
the simplest ways might be a Manhattan distance so and understands or Manhattan
및 이해 또는 맨하탄 있도록 간단한 방법은 맨해튼 거리를 수 있습니다
distance of the Institute
연구소의 거리
terms interchangeably simply what it does is you have a test image you're
용어는 상호 교환 단순히 무엇을 당신이있어 테스트 이미지를 가지고있다
interested in classifying and considered one single training image that we want
분류에 관심 고려 우리가 원하는 하나의 교육 이미지
to compare this image to see what we'll do is we'll element price compare all
우리가 무엇을 할 거 야 볼이 이미지를 비교하는 것은 우리가 요소 가격은 모든 비교 것입니다
the pics lollies so will form the absolute value differences and then we
찍어의 막대 사탕은 그러므로 절대 값의 차이를 형성하는 것이다 우리
just add all that up so we're just look at every single position or subtracting
그냥 우리가 모든 단일 위치 또는 감산을보고있는 모든 것을 추가 할
it off and see what the differences are increasingly special position adding it
그것은 오프 차이가 추가 점점 더 특별한 위치에 어떤 참조
all up and that's our similarity so these two images are for 56 different so
모든 걸 포기하고 우리의 유사성이다 그래서이 두 이미지는 그렇게 56 다른위한
we get a zero if we have identical images here just to show your code
우리가 코드를 보여주기 위해 여기에 동일한 이미지가 있다면 우리는 0을 얻을
specifically the way this would look like this is a full implementation of a
구체적으로는이 같을 것이다 방법은 전체 구현은
nearest-neighbor classifier and where I filled in the actual body of the two men
가장 가까운 이웃 분류와 나는 두 사람의 실제 몸에 충전 곳
talked about and what we do here at training time as we're giving this
에 대해 이야기하고 우리가주는 것 같이 우리는 훈련 시간에 여기에 무엇을
dataset X and Y which usually the note the labels so forgiving and labels all
레이블 그래서 용서 일반적으로 노트 모든 레이블 집합 X와 Y
we do is just assigned to the class instance methods so just remembered the
우리는 그냥 그냥 기억 클래스의 인스턴스 메소드에 할당 할
data nothing is being done I predict time though what we're doing here is
데이터 아무것도 우리가 여기서 무슨 일을하는지는 비록 내가 시간을 예측 수행되고 있지
we're getting newt test set of images X and I'm not going to go through a full
우리는 이미지의 X의 영원 테스트 세트를 받고있어 나는 전체를 통과하지 않을거야
details but you can see there's a for loop over every single test image
자세한하지만 당신은 모든 단일 테스트 이미지를 통해 for 루프 거기에 볼 수 있습니다
independently we're getting the distances to every single training image
독립적으로 우리는 매일 훈련 이미지의 거리를 받고있어
and notice that that's only a single line of vector I used Python code so in
그리고 그 하나의 벡터 라인 내가 그렇게 파이썬 코드를 사용하여 만의 통지
a single line of code were comparing that test image to every single training
단 한 줄의 코드는 매 훈련이 테스트 이미지를 비교 하​​였다
image in the database computing this distance in a previous slide and I think
내가 생각하고 이전 슬라이드에서이 거리를 계산 데이터베이스의 이미지
alike so that's a crisis code we didn't have to expend all those four loops that
그 위기 코드는 그래서 우리가 그 4 루프를 소비하지 않았다 모두 그
are involved in processing systems and then we compute the instance that is
처리 시스템에 참여하고 우리는 인스턴스를 계산하는
closest so we're getting them in index the index of the training that is has
가장 가까운 그래서 우리는 색인에 가지고있는 교육의 인덱스를을 받고있어
the lowest distance and then we'll just predicting for this image the label of
가장 낮은 거리와 그 다음 우리는 단지이 이미지 레이블에 대한 예측됩니다
whatever so here's a question for you in terms of the nearest neighbor classifier
그래서 여기에 어떤 것은 가장 가까운 이웃 분류의 관점에서 당신을위한 질문
how does its speed depend on the training data size what happens is a
어떻게 그 속도는 무슨 일하는 것은 인 훈련 데이터의 크기에 따라 달라 않습니다
scale up the training gear slower
느린 훈련 장비를 확장
yes it's actually it's actually really slow right because if I have I just have
내가 만약 내가 그냥 가지고 있기 때문에 예는 실제로는 실제로 아주 천천히 맞아입니다
to compare every single training sample independently so it's a little slow down
천천히 아래로 조금 그래서 독립적으로 하나 하나 훈련 샘플을 비교
and actually go as we go through the classes that this is actually backwards
우리는 클래스를 진행하면서이 거꾸로 실제로는 것을 실제로 이동
because what we really care about the most practical applications as we care
우리가 관심을 우리가 정말 가장 실용적인 응용 프로그램에 대한 관심이 무엇 때문에
about the test time performance of these classifiers that means that we want this
이 분류의 시험 시간 성능에 대해 그것은 우리가 원하는 것을 의미합니다
class to be very efficient at this time and so there's a tradeoff between really
클래스는이 시점에서 매우 효율적 그래서 정말 사이의 트레이드 오프있을 수 있습니다
how much computer we put on the train method and how much do we put in a good
우리는 기차 방식에 넣고 우리는 좋은에서 얼마나 넣을까요 얼마나 많은 컴퓨터
nearest neighbor is instant a train but then it's expensive a test and as we'll
가장 가까운 이웃 기차 인스턴트하지만 그것은 우리가 거​​ 같은 시험 비싼 및
see soon come that's actually flip this completely the other way around
곧 볼이 실제로 주변이 완전히 다른 방법으로 플립있어 올
will see that we do a huge amount of compute a train time will be training
우리가 컴퓨팅의 엄청난 양의 훈련을 할 것이다 기차 시간을 볼 것이다
commercial network system performance will be super efficient in fact it will
상업용 네트워크의 시스템 성능은 것 실제로 매우 효율적일 것이다
be constant amount of compute for every single test image with the constant
상수와 하나 하나 테스트 이미지 컴퓨팅의 일정 금액을 수
amount of computation no matter if you have a million billions or trillions
당신 만 수십억 또는 수조가있는 경우에 상관없이 계산의 양
training I'm just I'd like to have a trillion trillion trillion trillion just
난 그냥 해요 훈련은 내가 조 조 조 조를 그냥 가지고 싶습니다
no matter how large or trade deficit will do a complete custom computer to
아무리 크거나 무역 적자가 전체 사용자의 컴퓨터 작업을 수행하는 방법
classify any single testing sample so that's very nice practically speaking
즉 실질적으로 말하기 아주 좋은, 그래서 단일 테스트 샘플을 분류
now I'll just like to point out that there are ways of speeding up here saber
지금은 그냥 세이버 여기 가속화하는 방법이 있다는 것을 지적하고자합니다
classifiers there's these approximate nearest neighbor methods plan as an
이 대략 가까운 이웃 방법 거기 분류는 같은 계획
example library that people use up to practice that allows you to speed up
사람들이 그 연습을 위해 사용 예제 라이브러리는 속도를 할 수 있습니다
this process of nearest-neighbor matching but that's just a side note ok
가까운 이웃이 과정은 일치하지만 확인 그냥 보조 노트의
so let's go back to the design of the classifier we saw that we've defined
그래서 우리는 우리가 정의한 것을보고 분류의 디자인으로 돌아 가자
this distance and I arbitrarily chosen to show you the Manhattan distance which
내가 임의로 선택이 거리는 당신에게 맨해튼 거리를 표시 할
compares the difference of the absolute value there is in fact many ways you can
할 수있는 많은 방법이 사실상 존재 절대 값의 차이를 비교
formulate a distance metric and so there's many different choices of
측정 거리를 공식화 등의 다양한 선택이있다
exactly how we do this comparison another sim another choice to people
우리는이 비교를 정확히 어떻게 다른 사람들에게 다른 선택의 여지가 심
like to use in practice is what we call the Euclidean are ultra distance which
실제로 사용하려면 우리가 유클리드 울트라 거리입니다 부르는하다
instead sums up the differences in the sums of squares of these differences
대신에 이러한 차이의 제곱합의 차이를 요약
between images and so this choice
이미지 등이 선택 사이
that someone over there and back
그 이상이 다시 사람
ok so this choice of what how exactly computer distance it's a discrete choice
확인 그래서 어떤 방법을 정확하게 컴퓨터 거리의이 선택은 이산 선택이다
that we have control over that something we called hyper primary it's not really
우리는 우리가 차 하이퍼라는 뭔가를 제어 할 수 있는지 정말 아니에요
obvious how you set it it's a hyper parameters we have to decide later on
분명 당신이 그것을 설정하는 방법은 우리가 나중에 결정해야 하이퍼 매개 변수의
exactly how to set this somehow another sort of hybrid primary they'll talk
정확히 그들이 얘기하자 하이브리드 차의이 어떻게 든 다른 종류를 설정하는 방법
about in context of a classifier is when we generalize nearest neighbor to have
우리가 가지고 가까운 이웃을 일반화하는 경우에 대한 분류의 맥락에서
what we call a k nearest neighbor classifier so in a que horas neighbor
우리는 가장 가까운 이웃 분류 AK 전화 무엇 케 horas 이웃에 너무
classifiers that are retrieving for every test match the single nearest
모든 테스트를 위해 검색하는 분류는 가장 가까운 하나의 일치
train example will in fact retreat several examples and will have the new
사실 몇 가지 예를 후퇴합니다 예를 양성하고 새로운있을 것이다
majority vote over the closest to actually classified every test instance
가장 가까운 이상의 다수결은 실제로 모든 테스트 인스턴스를 분류합니다
so say a neighbor we would be retrieving the five most similar images in the
그래서 이웃이 우리가에있는 5 가장 유사한 이미지를 검색하는 것 말
training data and doing a majority vote of the labels here's a simple
훈련 데이터와 레이블의 과반수 투표를하고 여기에 간단
two-dimensional data set to illustrate the point so here we have a three-class
그래서 여기에 요점을 설명하기 위해 설정이 차원 데이터 우리는 세 클래스가
dataset and 2d and Here I am drawing what we call decision regions this
데이터 세트 및 2D와 여기에 우리가 결정 영역이 부르는 그리기입니다
nearest neighbor classifier here with this refers to is were truly trained
여기에 가장 가까운 이웃 분류는 정말 훈련을받은되는 의미
over there and we're coloring the entire to deplane by what class this nearest
우리는 전체를 색칠하고 거기 무슨 수업이 가까운에 의해 비행기에서 내리다하기
neighbor classifier with a sign that every single point suppose you don't
모든 단일 지점은 그렇지 가정 기호 이웃 분류
suppose you had a test example some more here than just saying that this would
당신은 단지이 것이라고 말하는 것보다 더 여기에 몇 가지 테스트 예를 들어 있다고 가정
have been classified as blue class based on the nearest neighbor you get personal
당신이 개인 얻는 가장 가까운 이웃을 기반으로 푸른 클래스로 분류 된
note that here is a point that is a green point inside the blue cluster and
점에 유의 푸른 클러스터 내부의 녹색 지점 인 점이며,
it has its own little region of class where it would have classified a lot of
그것이 많은의 분류했을 클래스 자체의 작은 영역을 갖는다
tests place around it as green because if anything to tell their than that
무엇이든 자신보다 그에게 경우 때문에 테스트는 녹색으로 주위에 배치
green point of the nearest neighbor now when you move to higher numbers for ke
가장 가까운 이웃의 녹색 점은 이제 애에 대한 높은 숫자로 이동할 때
such as five years neighbor classifier what you find is that the boundaries
당신이 무엇을 발견 같은 오년 이웃 분류기는 경계입니다
start to smooth out it's kind of nice effect where even that there's just one
한 거기 심지어 어디 좋은 효과 그것의 종류 부드럽게 시작
point
포인트
kind of randomly as noise and outliers in the blue cluster it's actually not
가지 무작위 실제로 아니다 푸른 클러스터의 소음과 아웃 라이어로
employing the predictions too much because we always are treating five
우리는 항상 다섯을 치료하기 때문에 너무 많은 예측을 채용
nearest neighbors and so they get to overwhelm the Greenpoint so in practice
가장 가까운 이웃은 그래서 그들은 실제로 그렇게 그린 포인트를 압도 얻을
you'll find that usually can your summer classifiers offer better better
당신이를 찾을 수 있습니다 일반적으로 여름 분류는 더 나은 제공 할 수 있습니다
performance at US time now but again the choice of k is again a hyper perimeter
이제 US시 성능 그러나 다시 K의 선택은 다시 경계 인 하이퍼
right so I'll come back to this in a bit just to show you an example of this look
내가 조금이 다시 올 거 바로 그래서 당신이보기의 예를 보여
like here I'm returning ten most similar examples they're ranked by their
여기처럼 나는 그들에 의해 위를 기록하고 열 가장 유사한 예를 반환하고있어 자신의
distance and I would actually do majority vote over these training
거리와 실제로 이러한 훈련을 통해 과반수 투표를 할 것
examples here to classify every test example here
여기 예제는 여기에 모든 테스트 예제를 분류합니다
ok so let's do a bit of questions here just consider what is the accuracy of
확인 그래서 여기에 단지의 정확성이 무엇인지 고려의 질문의 비트를하자
the north of a classifier on the training data when we're using Euclidean
우리는 유클리드을 사용하는 훈련 데이터에 대한 분류의 북쪽
distance so I suppose our test set is exactly the training data and we're
나는 우리의 테스트 세트는 정확히 훈련 데이터입니다 가정, 우리가있어 너무 거리
trying to find the accuracy in other words how many how often would we get
우리는 얼마나 자주를 얻을 얼마나 많은 즉 정확성을 찾기 위해 노력
the correct answer
정답
hundred-percent good ok among numerous yeah that's correct so we're always find
많은 중 확인을 백 퍼센트의 좋은 예 맞습니다 그래서 우리는 항상 찾을 수있어
a train example exactly on top of that test which has their own this does and
가 자신이 수행하고 정확하게 테스트의 상단에 기차 예
then it's like will be transferred over what if we're using the Manhattan
다음과 같은 우리가 맨해튼을 사용하는 경우 무엇을 통해 전송 될 것
distance that
거리가
Manhattan distance doesn't need sum of squares are you some absolute values
맨해튼 거리가 약간의 절대 값은 당신에게 있습니다 제곱의 합을 필요로하지 않는다
from differences it would it's just a question would be something like a good
차이에서 그것은 단지 문제는 좋은 같은 것 것 것
summer or keeping
여름이나 유지
attention ok what is the accuracy of the King your neighbor classifier trained it
관심을 확인 이웃 분류가 훈련 왕의 정확성은 무엇인가
is a cable spot if is it a hundred percent not necessarily get because
반드시 때문에하지 백 %가 그것을 경우 케이블 장소입니다
basically the points around you could overwhelm you even have your best
기본적으로 주변의 포인트는 당신이 당신의 최선을 압도 할 수
example is actually off the glass ok so we've discussed two choices of different
예를 들어 유리 떨어져 실제로 괜찮 그래서 우리는 서로 다른 두 가지 선택을 논의했습니다
premise we have just met Rick its high pressure in this case we're not sure how
전제 우리가이 경우에 릭에게 높은 압력을 만난 우리는 어떻게 확실하지 않다
to set it should be 1 23 10 and so on so we're not exactly sure how to set these
그렇게 우리는 이러한 설정하는 방법을 정확하게 확실하지에 1 23 10 이렇게해야 설정
in fact their problem dependent you'll find that you can't find consistently
사실에 따라 자신의 문제는 당신이 지속적으로 찾을 수 없습니다 찾을 수 있습니다
best choice for these high premise in some applications some case might look
일부 경우에 볼 수있는 몇 가지 응용 프로그램에서 이러한 높은 전제를위한 최선의 선택
better than other applications so we're not really sure how to set this so
우리가 이것을하도록 설정하는 방법을 정말 확실하지 않도록 다른 응용 프로그램보다 더 나은
here's an idea we have to basically try out to lots of different primers so I'm
여기에 우리가 기본적으로 난 그래서 다른 프라이머의 제비를 시도 할 생각이다
gonna do as I'm going to take my train data and then I'm going to try out lots
거 내가 나의 기차 데이터를 데리고 갈거야 다음 내가 많이 시도거야과 같이
of different parameters so I might just die and I try out cables 123456 2800 I
다른 매개 변수의 그래서 난 그냥 죽을 수와 나는 케이블 123456 2800 I을 시도
tried all the defendants metrics and whatever works best that's what I'll
즉 가장 적합한 무엇이든 모든 피고인 메트릭을 시도하고는 내가 정액의
take so that will work very well right lies in its not a good idea because ok
그래서 괜찮 때문에 좋은 생각에 아주 잘 오른쪽 거짓말을 작동 걸릴
so basically so basically yes so test data is your proxy for your
그래서 기본적으로 그래서 기본적으로 네 그래서 테스트 데이터에 대한 프록시 당신의
generalization of your order them you should not trust should the test data in
신뢰하지 않아야 주문 그들의 일반화해야 테스트 데이터에
fact you should forget that you ever have to Stata so it went 1 for giving
당신은 당신이 이제까지 STATA에있는 잊지해야 사실은 그래서주는 일을했다
your dataset always set aside the testator pretend you don't have it
데이터 집합은 항상 당신이 그것을 필요가 없습니다 척 유언자를 따로
that's telling you how will your organs generalizing to unseen data points and
그게 당신을 말하고 어떻게 것입니다 보이지 않는 데이터 점에 일반화 당신의 장기와
is important because you're trying to develop your algorithm and then you're
당신이 당신의 알고리즘을 개발하기 위해 노력하고 있기 때문에 중요합니다 그리고 당신은있어
hoping to eventually the planet and some setting and you liked understanding of
결국 지구와 몇 가지 설정을 할 희망 당신은 이해 좋아
exactly how will do I expect this to work in practice right and so you'll see
정확히 할 것입니다 어떻게 연습 오른쪽 작업이 예상 그래서 당신은 볼 수 있습니다
that for example sometimes you can perform very very well-intended about
예를 들어 때때로 당신은 매우 매우에 대해 잘 구성 수행 할 수있는
not generalize very well to test it on
아주 잘 일반화 그것을 테스트하지
you're overthinking someone a lot of this by 28 to 29 the requirement for
당신은 28 요구 사항 29에 의해 사람이 많이 지나친 것
this class so you should be quite familiar with this disease to most
이 클래스는, 그래서 당신은 가장이 질병에 매우 잘 알고 있어야합니다
extent this is kind of more and more overview for you but basically this test
범위이 당신을 위해 좀 더 많은 개요 그러나 기본적으로이 테스트입니다
data is used very sparingly forget that you have it instead what we do is we
데이터는 우리가 할 대신 무엇을 잊지 매우 드물게 사용된다
separate our training data into what we call folds so we separate safely use a
우리가 안전하게를 사용으로 구분하기 때문에 우리가 주름을 부르는에 우리의 훈련 데이터를 분리
five-fold validation so we use twenty percent of the training data as a
우리는 같은 트레이닝 데이터의 20 %를 사용할 수 있도록 5 배 검증
imagine such data and then we only training part of it and we test on we
데이터 및 그것의 우리는 교육 부분을 상상하고 우리는 우리의 테스트
just have two choices applied primarily on this validation set so I'm going to
그냥 내가 갈거야 그렇게 설정이 검증에 주로 적용되는 두 가지 선택이
train on my phone calls and try out different case and all the front of some
내 전화에 훈련과 다른 경우 일부의 모든 앞을 시도
clerics and whatever else if you're using approximate nearest neighbor yet
성직자와 아직 대략 가까운 이웃를 사용하는 경우 다른 어떤
many other choices you try it out see what works best on that validation data
당신이 그것을 시도 많은 다른 선택은 밖으로 그 검증 데이터에 가장 적합한 참조
if you're feeling uncomfortable because you have very few training data points
당신이 불편하게 느끼는 경우는 거의 훈련 데이터 포인트를 가지고 있기 때문에
people also sometimes used cross-validation where you actually get
당신이 실제로 얻을 곳 사람들은 때때로 교차 유효성 검사를 사용
to rate the choice of your test validation pulled across these choices
테스트 검증의 선택이 이러한 선택을 통해 뽑아 평가하기
so I'll first use for 124 for my training and try out on five and then I
그래서 내가 먼저 내 훈련 (124)에 사용할 수 있습니다 나는 다섯에 시도하고
cycled the choice of the validation pulled across all the five choices and I
검증의 선택이 모든 다섯 선택과 I에서 뽑아 순환
look at what works best across all the possible choices of my test fold and
내 테스트 배의 모든 가능한 선택을 통해 가장 적합한보고
then I just take whatever works best across all the possible scenarios
그때는 모든 가능한 시나리오를 통해 가장 적합한 무엇이든 취할
that's a front-runner cross validation set screw validation some practice the
그건 선두 주자 교차 검증 고정 나사 검증의 연습
way this would look like they were Cross building for K for nearest neighbor
이 그들과 같을 것이다 방법은 가장 가까운 이웃을 위해 K에 대한 크로스 건물이었다
classifier is we are trying out different values of K and this is our
분류 우리는 K의 다른 값을 시도하고 이것이 우리입니다
performance across five choices of the fold so you can see that for every
겹의 다섯 가지 선택에서 성능이 그래서 당신은 모든에 대한 것을 볼 수 있습니다
single case we have five data points there and then this is the accuracy so
하나의 경우 우리가 5 개의 데이터 지점을 가지고 다음이 정밀도가 그렇다
high is good and I'm plotting a line through the mean analyst Sean Arce for
높은 좋은 내가 평균 분석가 숀 Arce에 대한 통하여 선을 음모를 꾸미고 있어요
the standard deviations so we see here is that the performance goes up on the
표준 편차는 그래서 우리는 여기에서 볼 성능이 위로가는 것입니다
across these polls as you go up but at some point starr said idk so for this
이 여론 조사에서 당신은 가서 같이하지만, 어떤 점에서 스타는 말했다 이것을 그래서 나도 몰라
particular dataset it seems that K equal to 7 is the best choice so that's what
특정 데이터 세트는 그게 그래서 7과 동일 K 최고의 선택이 될 것 같다 무엇
I'll do this for all my hyperemesis also for the symmetric and so on I do my
나는 대칭과 내가 할에 모든 내 hyperemesis에 대해이 작업을 수행 할 수 있습니다 내
cross validation i promise i said i fix them evaluate a single time on the test
내가 약속 교차 검증은 내가 그들을 시험에서 하나의 시간을 평가하고 수정했다
site and whatever number I get to that's what I report as eight accuracy of a
내가 그에 도착 사이트와 어떤 수는 내가 여덟 정확도로보고 무엇을
king or some classifier on this dataset that's what goes into a paper that's
왕이나의 종이로가는 무슨이 데이터 세트에 대한 몇 가지 분류
what goes into our final report as long as the final generalization result of
무엇의 최종 일반화 결과만큼 우리의 최종 보고서로 전환
what you've done
무슨 짓을했는지
any questions about this basically it's about the statistics of the distribution
이에 대한 질문은 기본적으로는 분포의 통계에 관하여
of these data points in your label in your face and so sometimes it's hard to
라벨에 이러한 데이터 포인트 당신의 얼굴에 그래서 때때로의 그것은 하드의
say like you get whereas this picture you see roughly what happening as you
이 그림 반면 얻을처럼 당신으로 발생하는 약을 확인 말
get more cleanliness and more case and it just depends on how clunkier data
더 청결과 더 많은 경우를 얻을 수 있으며 얼마나 clunkier 데이터에 의존
service that's really what it comes down to is how
이 내려 오는 것을 정말 서비스는 어떻게
lobby is it or how specific is it I know that's very handy answer but that's
로비를하거나 그것을 어떻게 특정 그게 매우 편리 대답은 알고 있지만 그건
roughly what what that comes into so different datasets will have different
그 때문에 다른 데이터 세트는 다른 것에 와서 무엇을 대략 무엇
clicking us right now
지금 우리를 클릭
because
때문에
and different different datasets will require different choices and need to
다른 다른 데이터 세트는 다른 선택을 필요로해야합니다
see what works best if actually try out different algorithms
실제로 다른 알고리즘을 시도하는 경우에 작동하는 무슨이 가장 참조
you're not sure what's going to work best in your data the choice of your
당신은 당신의 데이터의 선택에서 가장 잘 작동하는 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 확실하지 않은 당신의
order is also kind of like hyper hammer so you're just not sure what works
당신이 어떤 작품 그냥 확실하지 않도록하기 위해 하이퍼 망치 같은 종류의도
different approaches will be different
다른 접근 방법이 다를 수 있습니다
generalization boundaries they look different and some data sets up the
일반화 경계는 서로 다른 모양과 일부 데이터가 설정하는
front structure than other some things work better than others
다른 것보다 앞 구조 몇 가지 다른 사람보다 더 잘 작동
just ran it tried out ok I just like to point out that king or something worse
그냥 난 그냥 그 왕 또는 더 나쁜 뭔가를 가리 키도록 좋아 좋아 밖으로 시도 실행
is no one basically uses this sunday going through this just doesn't get used
아무도 기본적으로 그냥 사용하지 않는이 통과하는이 일요일를 사용하지입니다
to this approach of really how this works with training just splits and so
이 훈련은 단지 분할 등 작동 정말 방법이 방법
on
...에
the reason this is never used as because first of all it's very inefficient but
그 이유는 이것이 우선 매우 비효율적이기 때문으로 사​​용하지 않고,
second of all this is my tracks all images which are very high dimensional
모든이의 두 번째 내 트랙 차원 높은 모든 이미지입니다
objects they acting very unnatural and intuitive ways I've done is taken in
개체는 그들은 내가에서 촬영 한 적이 매우 부자연스럽고 직관적 인 방법을 행동
order to limit and I change it in three different ways but all these three
순서는 제한하고 나는 세 가지 방법으로 변경하지만이 모든 세
different images here have actually the exact same distance to this one in an L
여기에 서로 다른 이미지는 L 실제로이 하나의 동일한 거리를
to Euclidean sense as I just think about this one here is slightly shifted to the
유클리드 감각에 난 그냥 여기 사람이 약간에 이동에 대해 생각하는
left it's dropped slightly and it's this is here are completely different because
그것은 약간 떨어있어 그것은이 여기의 왼쪽 이유로 인해 완전히 다른
these pixels are not matching up exactly and it's all introducing all these
이러한 픽셀은 정확 하 게 일치하지 않습니다 그것은 모든 모든을 소개하는 것
errors in your getting distance this one is slightly darkened so you get a small
당신은 작은을 얻을 수 있도록이 하나가 약간 어둡게하여 점점 거리의 오류
Delta across all special occasions and this one is untouched 60 distance eres
모든 특별 행사를 통해 델타이 하나의 손길이 닿지 않은 60 거리 ERES입니다
across everywhere except in those positions over there and that is taken
사방에서 저기 그 위치를 제외하고는 촬영
out critical pieces of the image and it doesn't the nearest neighbor classifier
아웃 임계 이미지 조각과 가장 가까운 이웃 분류를하지 않는다
will not be able to really tell the difference between these settings
정말 이러한 설정의 차이를 말할 수 없습니다
because it's based on these distances that don't really work very well in this
이이 거리를 기반으로하기 때문에 그 정말이 아주 잘 작동하지 않는다
case so very unintuitive things happen when you try to throw distances on very
당신은 매우에 거리를 던져하려고 할 때 경우 이렇게 아주 직관적 일이 일어날
high dimensional objects that's partly why we don't exist so in summary so far
우리가 지금까지 요약에 그렇게 존재하지 않는 이유를 부분적으로의 높은 차원 객체
we're looking at these classifications a specific case involving two different
우리는 이러한 분류에서 서로 다른 두를 포함하는 특정한 경우를 찾고
settings later in the class of Engineers neighbor classifier and the idea of
나중에 엔지니어 이웃 분류의 클래스와 아이디어의 설정
having different splits up your data and we have these high pressure hose that
최대 데이터를 다른 분할을 갖고 우리는 이러한 고압 호스를 그
will need to pick and we use Cross foundation for this usually most of the
선택해야하고 우리는이 일반적으로 대부분의 크로스 기반을 사용합니다
time people don't actually entire cross-validation they just have a single
시간 사람들은 단지 하나가 실제로 전체 교차 유효성 검사를 수행
validation
확인
and they try out on the validation set whatever works best in terms of the high
그들은 높은 측면에서 가장 적합한 어떤 검증 세트에 시도
premise and once you get the best have primaries you have a lead to single
전제하고 가장이 예비 선거를 일단 당신은 하나에 리드를
tenant just said so I'm going to go into the classification but any questions at
세입자는 그냥 분류에 갈하지만 질문에있어 그렇게 말했다
this point I see great we're going to look at Telenor classification this is a
나는 우리가 텔레 노어 분류 보는거야 좋은 볼이 시점이 인
point where we are starting to work towards commercial networks it'll be a
우리는이를 알 수있을 것입니다 상업 네트워크를 향해 작업을 시작하는 지점
series of lectures will snarl classification that will build up to an
강의 시리즈는 최대 만들 것이다 분류를 혼란 것
entire commercial network analyzing image I just like to say that motivated
전체 상용 네트워크 분석 이미지는 그냥 그 동기를 말씀 드리고
the class yesterday from a task-specific view this class is computer vision class
작업 별보기에서 클래스 어제이 클래스는 컴퓨터 비전 클래스입니다
interested in giving machines site and other way to motivate this class will be
기계 사이트 될 것이 클래스 동기를 부여하기 위해 다른 방법을 제공에 관심
from a model-based point of view in a sense that we're giving you guys
어떤 의미에서보기의 모델 기반 관점에서 그 우리는 너희들을 제공하고
watching guys about the plumbing and electrics these are wonderful algorithms
배관 및 전기에 대한 사람 보는이 멋진 알고리즘은
that you can apply to many different demands not just some particularly over
당신은 단지 일부, 특히 위에 다양한 요구에 적용 할 수있는
the last few years we saw that neural networks can not only see that's what
지난 몇 년 동안 우리는 신경 네트워크는 그 무엇입니까 볼 수없는 것을보고
you'll learn a lot about this class but he also here there is quite a bit in a
이 클래스에 대해 많은 것을 배울 것이다 그러나 그는 또한 여기에 꽤있다
speech recognition now so when you talk to your phone does not work they can
당신이 휴대 전화로 이야기 할 때 음성 인식은 지금 그들이 할 수있는 작동하지 않습니다
also do machine translation so here you are feeding neural network a set of
또한 그래서 여기에 기계 번역을 당신은 세트의 신경 네트워크를 먹이
words one by one in English and the neural network produces the translation
영어 하나 신경망로 단어 하나는 번역을 생산
in print or whatever else target language you have to perform control so
인쇄 또는 어떤 다른 대상 언어에 그렇게 제어를 수행 할 필요가
we've seen your network applications and manipulate in the robots manipulation
우리는 당신의 네트워크 응용 프로그램을 볼 수 및 로봇 조작에 조작 한
and playing at a party gains work learn how to play three games just by seeing
및 파티 이익의 직장에서 재생하면 확인하여 세 가지 게임을 바로 재생하는 방법
the rockets will set the screen and we seem to be very successful in the
로켓은 화면을 설정하고 우리는 매우 성공적인 것으로 보인다
variety of domains and even more than a bit here and we're uncertain exactly
도메인의 다양성과 여기에 조금보다 더 우리는 정확히 확실치
where this will take us and then I'd like to also say that we're exploring
어디이 우리를 취할 것 그리고, 나는 또한 우리가 탐구하고 있다는 말을하고 싶습니다
ways for lyrics do think that this is very henry VIII is just wishful thinking
이것은 매우 헨리 VIII이라고 생각합니까 가사에 대한 방법은 소망 적 사고입니다
but there are some hints that maybe they can do that as well
하지만 어쩌면 그들은뿐만 아니라 그렇게 할 수있는 몇 가지 힌트가있다
neural networks are very nice because they're just fun modular things to play
그들이 연주하는 재미 모듈 일이기 때문에 신경 네트워크는 아주 좋은입니다
with when I think about working with their networks I kind of this picture
나는이 사진의 자신의 네트워크와 I 종류의 작업에 대해 생각할 때와
comes to mind for me here we have a neural networks practitioner and she's
여기에 나를 위해 마음에 오는 우리는 신경 네트워크 개업이 그녀입니다
building what looks to be a roughly 10 layer at this point
보이는 것을 만드는 것은이 시점에서 대략 10 층이 될 수 있습니다
it's very fun really the best way to think about playing with their looks
정말 자신의 외모와 함께 연주에 대해 생각하는 가장 좋은 방법은 매우 재미
like Lego blocks you'll see that we're building these little function pieces
레고 블록처럼 우리가이 작은 기능 조각을 구축하는 것을 볼 수 있습니다
you look a lot so we can stuck together to create entire architectures and then
당신은 많은 그래서 우리는 다음 전체 아키텍처를 만들어 함께 붙어 수 있습니다 봐
very easily talk to each other and so we can just create these modules in
아주 쉽게 서로 이야기하고 그래서 우리는 이러한 모듈을 만들 수 있습니다
Stockton together and play with this very easily won work that I think
스톡턴 함께 내가 생각이 아주 쉽게 승리 작업 플레이
exemplifies this is my homework on which captioning from roughly a year ago so
예시이 내 숙제입니다 대략 년 전에 그렇게로부터의 자막에
here in the task was to take an image and you're trying to get to work to
여기에 작업의 이미지를 촬영했다 당신은에 일을 얻기 위해 노력하고
produce a sentence description of the image so for example the top left these
예를 들어 상단이 왼쪽 있도록 이미지의 문장 설명을 생산
artists set results would say that this is many black shirt was playing guitar
예술가는 결과이 많은 검은 셔츠는 기타를 연주 한 것을 말할 것입니다 설정
or a construction worker in Orange City West is working on the road and so on so
또는 오렌지 시티 웨스트에서 건설 노동자 등등 그래서 도로에 노력하고있다
they can look at the image and create this description of every single image
그들은 영상을보고 하나 하나 이미지의이 설명을 만들 수 있습니다
and when you go to the details of this model the way this works is we're taking
이 모델의 세부 사항에 길을 갈 때 이것은 우리가 복용하고있다 작품
the convolutional neural network which we know so there's two modules here in
우리가 알고있는 길쌈 신경망 그래서 여기에 두 개의 모듈에있다
this system diagram for image capturing model which we can accomplish on your
우리가 달성 할 수있는 촬상 모델이 계통도하여
network which we know can see we're taking a recurrent neural network which
우리가 알고있는 네트워크는 우리가 재발 성 신경 네트워크를 복용하고 볼 수있는
we know is very good and modeling sequences in this case sequences of
우리는이 경우 시퀀스에 아주 좋은 및 모델링 시퀀스 알고
words that will be describing the image and then just as if we were playing with
이미지를 설명하는 것 그리고 우리가 가지고 노는 것처럼 말
LEGOs we take those two pieces and we stick them together its corresponding to
레고 우리는 그 두 가지를 가지고 우리는 함께 그에 대응을 스틱
this arrow here in between the two modules in these networks learned to
이러한 네트워크에있는 두 개의 모듈 사이에서 여기 화살표에 배운
talk to each other and in the process of trying to describe the images these
이러한 이미지를 설명하기 위해 서로와 노력의 과정에서 대화
gradients will be flown through the comedy show that work on the phone
그라디언트는 휴대 전화에서 작동 코미디 쇼를 통해 비행한다
system will be adjusting itself to better see the images in order to
시스템은 더하기 위해 이미지를보고 자신을 조정하는 것
describe them at the end and so this whole system will work together as one
말을 설명하고 그래서이 모든 시스템은 하나 같이 함께 작동합니다
so we'll be working towards this model will actually come to this class will
그래서 우리는 실제로이 클래스에 올 것이다이 모델을 위해 노력 할 것이다 것
have a full understanding exactly off both this part and this part about
바로이 부​​분이 부분에 대해 모두 떨어져 전체 이해를
halfway through the course roughly you'll see how that instructional model
중간 과정을 통해 대략 당신은 어떻게 교육 모델을 볼 수 있습니다
works but that's just a motivation for really what we're building up to and
그 정말 우리가 구축하고있는 것에 대해 그냥 의욕이다 제외한 작동
you're like really nice models to work with ok but for now back to see 410 and
당신이 확인 작업을하지만 지금은 다시 410을보고 정말 좋은 모델처럼하고있어
all your classification
모든 분류
just remind you are working with this dataset 2000 and Justin labels and we're
당신이이 데이터 집합 2000 작업 저스틴 라벨된다 나게 우리는있어
going to approach your classification is from what we call a parametric approach
당신의 분류에 접근하려고하는 것은 우리가 파라 메트릭 방식 부르는에서입니다
can remember that we just discussed now is something an instance of what we call
우리가 지금 논의 된 것을 기억하는 것은 무엇인가 우리가 부르는의 인스턴스
nonparametric approach there's no parameters that we're going to be
비모수 적 접근 방법은 우리가 될거야 매개 변수가 없습니다
optimizing over this distinction will become clearer and human it's also
이러한 구분을 통해 최적화하는 것은 명확하게 인간은 또한의 뜻
apparent to the project we're doing is worth
우리가하고있는 프로젝트에 명백한 가치가있다
thinking about constructing a function that takes an image and produces the
이미지를 가져와을 생성하는 기능을 구성에 대해 생각
scores for classes right this is what we want to do you want to take any image
클래스에 대한 점수는 바로이 어떤 이미지를 수행해야 할 우리가해야 할 것입니다
and we'd like to figure out which one of the ten plus it is so we'd like to write
우리는 열 중 어느 하나를 파악하고 싶습니다 플러스 그렇게 우리가 쓰고 싶은된다
down the function and expression that takes an image and gives you those two
이미지를 소요하고 당신에게 그 두 가지를 제공하는 기능과 표현 아래로
numbers but the expression is not only function of that image but critically
숫자 만 표현은 매우뿐만 아니라 그 이미지의 기능 만입니다
ill be also a function of these parameters that are called W sometimes
때때로 병 W라고 이들 파라미터의 함수일
also called the weights so really it's a function that goes from 3072 numbers
또한 무게라고 그래서 정말은 3072 번호로 이동하는 기능입니다
which make up this image to 10 numbers that's what we're doing we're defining a
10 숫자에이 이미지를 우리는 우리가 정의하고 무슨 일을하는지있어 그 구성하는
function and we'll go through several choices of this function in this in the
기능 그리고 우리는이이 기능의 몇 가지 선택을 통해 이동합니다
first case will look at later functions and then extended to control it works
첫 번째 경우는 나중에 기능을보고 한 후 작동을 제어하도록 확장됩니다
and then we'll extend that to get commercial networks but intuitively what
그리고, 우리는 상업 네트워크 그러나 직관적으로 무엇을 얻기 위해 그 연장합니다
we're building up to is that what we'd like is when we put this image through
우리를 구축하고 우리를 통해이 이미지를 둘 때 우리가 원하는 것은이다
our function we'd like the 10 numbers that correspond to the scores of the 10
우리의 기능 우리는 10의 점수에 해당하는 10 숫자를 싶습니다
closest would like the number that corresponds to the cat class to be high
가장 가까운 높은 것으로 고양이 클래스에 해당하는 번호를 싶습니다
and all the other numbers to be low and will have we don't have a choice over X
다른 모든 숫자는 낮은하고있을 것이다 우리는 X를 통해 선택의 여지가 없어
that acts as our image that's given a choice over W you will be free to set
즉, 사용자가 설정하는 무료입니다 (W) 이상 선택의 여지가 주어진 것 우리의 이미지의 역할
aside whatever we want and we want will want to set it to let this function
어떤을 제외하고 우리가 원하는 우리는이 기능을 허용하도록 설정하는 것이 좋습니다 싶어
gives us the correct answers for every single image in our training data that's
의 우리의 훈련 데이터의 모든 하나의 이미지에 대한 우리에게 정답을 제공합니다
roughly the approach we're building towards suppose that we use the simplest
우리는 간단한 사용하는 것이 우리 가정하는 방향으로 구축하고 거의 접근
the simplest just a linear classification here so X is our image in
X 그래서 여기에 간단한 단지 선형 분류는 우리의 이미지입니다
this case wrongdoing as I'm taking this array this image that makes up the cat
이 경우 잘못은 내가 고양이를 구성하는이 영상이 배열을 취하고로
and I'm stretching out with all the pixels in that image into a giant column
나는 거대한 컬럼에 해당 이미지의 모든 픽셀 뻗어있어
vector so that there is a column vector of 3072 numbers and so if you know your
3072 번호 등의 열 벡터가되도록 벡터 당신이 알고있는 경우
matrix vector operations which you should that's a prerequisite for this
당신이이을위한 전제 조건입니다한다 행렬 벡터 연산
class that there is just a matrix multiplication which should be familiar
잘 알고 있어야합니다 단지 행렬 곱셈이 있다는 클래스
with and basically we're taking X which is a 3072 muscle column vector we're
와 기본적으로 우리는 우리가있어 3072 근육의 열 벡터이다 X를 취하고있어
trying to get 10 numbers and it no longer function so you can go backwards
(10) 번호를 얻으려고 노력하고 당신은 뒤로 더 이상 기능을 갈 수 있도록
and figure out the dimensions of this w are basically 10 by 3072 so there are
이 w의 크기는 3072 그래서 거기에 기본적으로 10입니다 파악
30,000 772 202 numbers that goes into W and that's what we have control over
즉 W로 전환하고 30,000 772 202 번호는 우리가 통제 할 수있는 무엇
that's what we have to tweak and find what works
그것은 우리가 조정할 및 작동 찾을 필요가 무엇
so those are the parameters in this particular case when I'm leaving out is
그래서 사람들은 내가 밖으로 떠날거야이 특정한 경우에 매개 변수가되고 있습니다
there's also an appended + be sometimes so you have a bias these biases are
또한 끝에 추가 된 거기에 + 이러한 편견은 편견을 가지고, 그래서 때로는 수
against 10 more parameters and we have to also find those so usually in a
10 개 이상의 매개 변수에 대해 우리는 또한 보통 사람들을 찾을 수있다
linear classifier have a WNB we have to find exactly what works best and this
선형 분류 우리가 가장 잘 작동 정확히 찾아 가지고 WNB을 가지고이
baby is not a function of the image that's just independent waits on the on
아기는 온에 그냥 독립적 인 대기의 이미지의 함수가 아니다
how likely any one of those just might be to go back to your question if you
가능성을 그 중 하나는 당신의 질문에 다시 갈 수 있습니다 당신이 경우
have a very unbalanced datasets for so maybe you have mostly cats but some dogs
어쩌면 당신은 대부분의 고양이 있지만 일부 개를위한 매우 불균형 데이터 집합을
or something like that then you might expect that the cat the bias for the
또는 그런 일이 당신은 기대할 수있는 고양이에 대한 편견이
catalyst might be slightly higher because by default the classifier once
한번 분류를 기본 때문에 촉매는 약간 높을 수 있습니다
to predict the catalyst unless something comes to the otherwise something in the
뭔가에 다른 뭔가를 제공하지 않는 한 촉매를 예측하는
image of God this otherwise I think that's more concrete I just like to
하나님의 형상이, 그렇지 않으면 나는 내가 단지에 같은보다 구체적인 생각
break it down but of course I can't visualize it very explicitly width 3072
그것을 분해하지만 물론 나는 그것이 매우 명시 적으로 3072 폭 시각화 할 수 없습니다
numbers so imagine that our input image 1024 pixels and imagine so more pics
숫자는 그래서 우리의 입력 이미지 1024 픽셀 및 그래서 더 많은 사진을 상상 상상
also stressed out in the column X and imagine that we have three classes so
또한 열 X에 스트레스를 우리는 세 가지 클래스 정도가 상상
red green and blue costs or a cat adoption process so in this case W will
적색, 녹색, 청색의 비용이나이 경우 W에서 매우 고양이 입양 처리합니다
be only a three by for matrix and what we're doing here is we're trying to
단지 매트릭스와 우리가 여기서 일을하는지에 대한 의해 세 가지가 우리가하려는하다
compute the score of this major acts so this is major application going on here
그래서이 주요 응용 프로그램은 여기 주요 행위의 점수를 계산하는 일이야
to give us the output of path which is this course we got the three scores for
우리에게 우리가 세 가지 점수를 가지고이 과정은 경로의 출력을 제공합니다
three different classes so this is random setting up w just running mates
세 가지 다른 클래스 그래서 이것은 단지 실행 동료 w 임의 설정까지입니다
here and we'll get some scores some particularly can see that with this this
여기 우리는 약간의 점수가 일부 특히이 이것과 저것을 볼 수있는거야
setting up w is not very good right because with this setting up w Marquette
때문에 마켓 w이 설정을 최대로 아주 좋은 옳지 않다 승 설정
score of 96 is much less than any of the other classes right so this was not
96의 점수가 다른 클래스들보다 훨씬 적은 바로 그래서이 아니었다
correctly classified for this training image so that's not a very good
그것은 매우 좋지 않다 그래서 올바르게 교육 이미지 분류
classifier so we want to change a different double
분류는 그래서 우리는 다른 배를 변경하려면
want to use a different W so that that score comes up higher than the other
그 스코어가 다른 것보다 더 위로 오도록 다른 W를 사용할
ones but we have to do that consistently across the entire training such examples
사람은 그러나 우리는 전체 교육 등의 예에서 일관되게 그렇게해야
but one thing to notice here as well as the basically W
하지만 한 가지가 기본적으로 W뿐만 아니라 여기주의 사항
it's this function is in parallel evaluating all the tenant classifiers
그것은 모든 세입자 분류 평가를 병렬로이 함수이야
but really there are ten independent classifiers
하지만 정말 열 독립적 인 분류가 있습니다
to some extent here and every one of these classifiers like say the cats
여기에 어느 정도 이러한 분류의 모든 일에 고양이 말을 좋아한다
classifier is just a first row of W here right in the first row and the first
분류기 여기 오른쪽 첫 번째 행과 첫 번째의 W 단지 최초의 행
bias gives you can't score and the dog classifier is the second row W and the
바이어스는 득점 할 수 있습니다 및 개 분류는 두 번째 행의 W하고있다
ship's quarter the ship + 500 W W matrix has all these different classifier
선박의 분기 배 + 500 WW 행렬은 모든 다른 분류가
stacked and rose and they're all being docked product and with the image to
스택과 장미 그리고 그들은 모든 제품을 도킹 및 이미지와 되 고있어
give you this course so here's a question for you what does a linear
그래서 여기에 당신이 과정을 제공 선형을 무엇을 당신을 위해 질문
classifier do in English we saw the functional form sticking is doing this
분류 영어로 할 우리는 함수 형태의 부착이를하고있다 보았다
funny operation there what was really interpret and English somehow what this
정말 어떻게 든 어떤이를 해석하고 영어 있었는지가 재미 작업
is doing
하고있다
X being a high-dimensional data point and W is really putting plains through
X되는 높은 차원 데이터 포인트와 W는 정말 통해 평야를두고있다
the site and come back to that interpretation of it but either way can
사이트는 그 해석에 돌아오고 있지만, 어느 쪽이든은 할 수
we think about this team way where every single one of these rows of W
우리는이 팀 방법에 대해 생각 어디 W의 이러한 행의 모든​​ 하나 하나
effectively is like this template that we're not talking with the image and I
효율적으로 우리가 이미지와 I과 이야기하지 않는이 템플릿처럼
dot product is really a way of like natural up seeing what what Alliance get
내적 정말하는 방법입니다 같은 얼라이언스 무엇을 얻을 것을보고까지 자연
to what other ways
어떤 다른 방법으로
two positions because what we can do is some of the spatial positions index if
우리가 할 수있는 것은 공간의 위치 인덱스의 경우 일부이기 때문에 두 위치
we have zero weights then the classifier would be
우리는 분류가 될 것 제로 가중치가
doesn't care what's in part of image so 50 waits for this part here then nothing
여기이 부분은 다음 아무것도 이미지 때문에 50 대기의 일부에 무슨 상관하지 않는다
affected but for some other parts of the image of you have positive or negative
영향을하지만 당신의 이미지의 다른 부분에 대한 양 또는 음이
weights something's gonna happen there and contribute to the score in other
무게는 뭔가거야이 일어날 등의 점수에 기여
ways of describing a space to a label space
라벨 공간의 공간을 기술하는 방법
so the question so this image as a three-dimensional terrain where we have
그래서 질문이 우리가 가진 입체 지형 등 때문에 이미지
all these channels you just a stretcher doubts all the you stretch it out in
그냥 들것이 의심이 모든 채널을 모든 당신은 그것을 스트레칭
whatever way you like say you start the red green and blue portions side-by-side
당신이 좋아하는 어떤 방법은 녹색 빨간색과 파란색 부분을 나란히 시작하는 말
only you stretch it out in whatever way you like but in a consistent way across
단지 당신은 당신이 좋아하는 어떤 방법으로하지만, 일관된 방법으로 그것을 스트레칭
all the images you figure out a way to serialize in which way you want to read
모든 이미지는 당신이 읽을 수있는 방법으로 직렬화하는 방법을 알아낼
off the pics also used to call him
또한 그에게 전화하는 데 사용되는 사진 오프
ok ok so let's say we have a for pixel grayscale image which is the terrible
확인 확인 그래서이 끔찍한 저희는 픽셀 그레이 스케일 이미지의가 있다고 가정하자
example you might think it i dont wanna confuse people especially because
예를 들어 당신은 내가 싶어 사람들, 특히 때문에 혼동하지 말아 그것을 생각
someone pointed out to me later after I made this figure that red green and blue
내가 적색, 녹색, 청색이이 그림을 만든 후 사람이 나중에 나에게 지적
are two color channels but here to red green and blue course on the closest
가장 가까운 두 개의 색상 채널 그러나 여기 적색, 녹색, 청색의 과정에 있습니다
this is a complete screw-up on my part so I apologize not color channels just
내가하지 색상 채널 그냥 사과 있도록이 내 부분에 완전한 나사 - 최대
three different colored closest sorry about that okay
그 괜찮에 대한 세 가지 다른 색깔의 가장 가까운 죄송합니다
large exactly how do we make this all be a single sized a column vector
큰 정확히 우리가 모두 하나의 크기의 열 벡터가 될 수 있도록 어떻게
the answer is you always always resize images to be basically the same size we
대답은 항상 항상 기본적으로 같은 크기의 우리로 이미지 크기를 조정하다
can't easily deal with different size than just a weekend we might go into
쉽게 우리가 들어갈 수있는 그냥 주말보다 다른 크기를 처리 할 수​​ 없습니다
that later but the simplest thing to think of it as just resize every single
나중에 그러나 가장 간단한 것은 단지 하나 하나의 크기를 조정라고 생각합니다
image to exact same size as the simplest thing because we want to ensure that all
우리가 모든 것을 보장하기 원하기 때문에 이미지가 간단한 것은 동일 크기를 정확하기
of them are kind of comparable of the same stuff so that we can make these
그들의 종류의 우리가 이것들을 할 수 있도록 동일한 물건의 필적
columns and we can analyze the school patterns that are aligned in the space
열과 우리는 공간에 정렬 학교 패턴을 분석 할 수 있습니다
in fact state of the art collectors the way they actually work on this is the
당해 수집기 사실 상태가 실제로 작동하는 방법이있다
only one square images so if you have a very long and these methods will
하나의 사각형 이미지가 매우 긴을 가지고있는 경우 이러한 방법 것 때문에
actually work worse because many of them what they do is to squash it that's what
그들 중 많은 사람들이 그들이 할 것은 그 무엇을의 IT 스쿼시하기 때문에 실제로 나쁜 일
we do still works fairly well so I feel very long like panorama just tried to
우리는 내가 단지에 노력 파노라마처럼 매우 긴 느낌 때문에 여전히 잘 공정하게 작동 할
put that somewhere like some online service chances are my work worse
일부 온라인 서비스의 기회가 더 내 일처럼 어딘가에 넣어
because they'll probably want to put it through come that they will make it a
그들은 아마도 그들이 그것을 할 것을 온을 통해 그것을 넣을 것이기 때문에
square because these comments always work on squares you can make them work
이러한 의견은 항상 사각형에서 작동하기 때문에 광장 당신은 그들이 일을 할 수 있습니다
on anything but that's just practice what happens usually any other questions
그건 그냥 일반적으로 다른 질문이 무슨 연습이야 아무것도하지만에
are interpreting the W the pacifier yeah yeah so each image get through this
젖꼭지 승을 해석하는 것은 그래 각각의 영상이 통과
anyone else would like to interpret this or so another way to actually put it one
하고 싶은 다른 사람이 해석하는 정도 다른 방법은 실제로 그것을 하나를 넣어
way that I didn't hear but it's also a nice way of looking at it is that
방법 나는 듣지 않았다 그러나 그것은 또한이다보고의 좋은 방법 있음
basically every single score is just a weighted sum of all the pixel values and
기본적으로 모든 단일 스코어가 모든 화소 값들의 단순한 가중 합이고
the image and these rates are we get to choose those eventually but I just a
이미지와 이러한 비율은 우리가 결국 그 선택에 도착하지만 난 그냥
giant weighted sum it's really all it's doing is it's coming up colors right
거대한 가중 합은 정말 그것이 바로 색상을오고있다하고있어 전부
it's coming up colors at different spatial positions so one way to one way
그렇게 하나의 방법 한 가지 방법으로 서로 다른 공간 위치에서 색상을오고
that was brought up in terms of how we can interpret this w classified concrete
그 우리가 분류 콘크리트 승이 해석 할 수있는 방법의 측면에서 자랐다
is that it's kind of like a bit like a template matching thing so here's what
그렇게 여기에 템플릿 매칭 것 같은 비트가 무엇을의 가지처럼이다
I've done is I trained classifier and I have a show you how to do that yet but I
나는 분류를 훈련 한 적이 그리고 당신이 그것을 수행하는 방법 쇼가 아직 있지만
trained my weight matrix and then come back to the second I'm taking out every
내 가중치 행렬을 훈련 한 다음 다시 두 번째로 돌아와 I 밖으로 가지고있어 모든
single one of those rows that we've learned every single classifier and I'm
우리가 난 모든 단일 분류를 배운 그 행을 하나 하나
reshaping in back to an end
끝으로 다시 재편
so that I can visualize it so I'm taking it originally just a giant blow-up 3072
나는 그것을 시각화 할 수 있도록 그래서 나는 원래 그냥 거대한 블로우 업 3072을 데려 갈거야
numbers I we ship it back to the image to undo the distortion have done and
우리는 왜곡을 취소 할 이미지로 다시 발송 번호 내가 수행하고
then I have all these templates and so for example what you see here is that
나는이 모든 템플릿이 때문에 예를 들어 당신이 여기에 참조하는 것입니다
plane it's like a blue blob here the reason you see blue blob is that if you
면 그것은 당신이 파란색 얼룩을 볼 수있는 이유는 여기에 파란색 얼룩 같은가요 당신 경우
looked at the color channels of this plane template you'll see that in the
당신은에있는 것을 볼이 비행기 템플릿의 색상 채널에서 보았다
blue channel you have lots of positive weights because those positive weights
파랑 채널 당신은 긍정적 인 무게의 제비가 그 양의 무게 때문에
if they see me values then they interact with those and they get a little
그럼 그들이 나에게 값을 볼 경우 그들은 사람들과 상호 작용하고 그들은 조금 얻을
contribution to the score so this plane classifiers really just counting up the
점수에 기여 그래서이 비행기 분류 정말 그냥 계산
amount of blue stuff in the image across all these special occasions and if you
모든 특별 행사에서하고있는 경우 이미지의 파란색 물건의 양
look at the red and green channel for the plane classifier you might find a
당신이를 찾을 수있는 평면 분류의 빨간색과 녹색 채널을보고
zero values or even negative values right that's the plan classifier
0 값 또는 음의 값 바로 그 계획의 분류입니다
price for all these other images to say a frog you can almost see the template
가격이 모든 다른 이미지가 개구리 말을하는 당신은 거의 템플릿을 볼 수 있습니다
of Prague their right to it looking for some green starfish green stuff has
프라하의 그것 권리는 녹색 물건이 일부 녹색 불가사리를 찾고
positive weights in here and then we see some brown starfish things on the side
긍정적 여기에 무게와 그 다음 우리는 측면에 약간의 갈색 불가사리 사물을
so if that gets butt over an image and dot product it will get a high score one
그 이미지와 내적 위에 엉덩이를 얻을 경우 그래서 높은 점수를 얻을 것이다
thing to note here is a look at this
여기에서 주목해야 할 것은 이것 좀입니다
the car classifier that's not a very like nice template of a car also hear
또한 듣고 자동차의 아주 같은 좋은 템플릿 아닙니다 차 분류
the horse looks a bit weird what's up that was the car looking wherein lies
말은 즉, 상기 거짓말을 찾고 차가이었다까지 무슨 조금 이상한 보인다
the horse looking weird yeah yeah basically that's what's going in the
보고 말 이상한 그래 기본적으로 그가에 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지의 예
data the horses someone facing left somewhere right and this classifier
데이터는 말 누군가가 어딘가에 오른쪽이 분류 왼쪽 직면
really is not very powerful classifier and has to combine the two modes it has
실제로 매우 강력한 분류가 아니고,이있는 두 가지 모드를 결합하는
to do both things at the same time staying up with us two headed horse in
두 향하고 말에 우리와 함께 머물 동시에 두 일을하는
there and you can in fact say that just when this result there's probably more
거기에이 결과는 아마 더있을 바로 그 때 당신은 실제로 그런 말을 할 수 있습니다
left facing horses in seaport in the right because the stronger they're also
강한 그들은 또한이기 때문에 오른쪽에있는 항구에서 말을 왼쪽에 직면
for car right we can have a car like 45 degrees to the left or right or front
자동차의 권리를 위해 우리는 왼쪽이나 오른쪽 또는 전방 45도 같은 차를 가질 수있다
and this classifier here is the optimal way of mixing across like merging all
여기에이 분류 모든 병합 같은에서 혼합하는 최적의 방법입니다
those modes into a single template because that's where forcing it to do
그 때문에 하나의 템플릿에 해당 모드가 여기서 할 그것을 강요
what we're actually doing that's and neural networks they don't have this
그들은이없는 우리가 실제로 그건 일을하는지와 신경망
downside they can actually have in principle they can have a template for
실제로 원칙적으로 할 수 있습니다 단점은 그들에 대한 템플릿을 가질 수있다
this car that card upcoming combined across them for giving them more power
카드가 그들에게 더 많은 힘을주고 그들을 통해 결합 곧이 차
to actually carry out this classification more properly but for now
실제로 더 적절하지만 지금이 분류를 수행하는
we are constrained by this
우리는이 제약된다
question
문제
yes something so a train time we would not be taken just exactly what will be
예 뭔가 그래서 우리가 정확하게 수행되지 않을 것이다 기차 시간이 될 것인가
generating them stretching them stealing them and we'll be putting all that
그들이 그들을 훔쳐을 스트레칭과 우리가 모든 것을 바꾸어됩니다 생성
that's going to become a huge part of getting to work very well so yes I will
즉, 그래 난 것 때문에 아주 잘 작동 점점의 큰 부분이 될 것
be doing a huge amount of that stuff for everything will change that we're going
우리가 가고 있다는 것을 변경됩니다 모두를위한 그 물건의 엄청난 금액을 수행 할 수
to elucidate many other training examples of ships since rotates and
회전하기 때문에 선박의 다른 많은 교육 사례를 규명하고,
stews and that works much better how these templates chain taking the average
스튜와 이러한 템플릿 체인 평균을 복용하는 방법이 훨씬 더 잘 작동
person so you want to explicitly set a template and the way your set the
사람 당신은 방법 당신의 세트를 명시 적으로 템플릿을 설정하고 싶은 있도록
template is your average across all the images and that becomes your template
템플릿은 모든 이미지에 걸쳐 평균이고, 그 템플릿된다
yeah so this classifier it binds they would do something similar I would guess
그래 그래서이 분류는 그들이 내가 추측하는 것입니다 비슷한 할 것이다 결합
it would work worse because the classifier when you look at its Michael
분류 당신은 마이클 볼 때 있기 때문에 더 작동합니다
formerly what it optimizes for it I don't think he would have a minimum of
이전에 그것을 위해 최적화 무엇 나는 그가 최소있을 것입니다 생각하지 않습니다
what you described in just a min of the images but that would be like intuitive
당신이 이미지의 단지 분에 설명하지만 직관적 같은 것
Lee decent heuristic to perhaps that awaits in the initialization or split
에 리 괜찮은 발견 아마도 그 초기화 또는 분할에 기다립니다
something related to it
그것은 어떤 관련
yeah yeah but we might be going to that I'll be able to return to their several
그래하지만 우리는 내가 그들의 몇 가지로 돌아갈 수있을거야 해당 갈 수 있습니다
several things
몇 가지
different colors red which is saying that there's probably more red cars in
에 아마 빨간색 자동차가 있다는 것을 말하고 다른 색상의 빨간색
the dataset and it may not work for you in fact yellow cards might be for this
데이터 세트는과 노란색 카드는이를 위해 수 있습니다 실제로 당신을 위해 작동하지 않을 수 있습니다
time so this thing just does not have capacity to do all of that which is why
시간은 그래서이 일을 그냥 이유입니다이 모든 것을 할 수있는 능력이 없습니다
the powerful enough it can capture all these different modes correctly and so
제대로 그래서 모든 다른 모드를 캡처 할 수있는 충분히 강력한
this will just go after the numbers there's more red cars that's where it
이것은 단지 어디있어 그 이상의 빨간색 차를 거기에 숫자 후 이동합니다
will go if this was grayscale I'm not sure if that would work better he'll
이 그레이 스케일 인 경우 그 그가거야 더 잘 작동한다면 잘 모르겠어요 갈 것입니다
come back to that actually you might expect as I mentioned for imbalanced
내가 불균형에 대해 언급 한 바와 같이 실제로 당신이 예상 다시 그에게 올
datasets what you might expect
당신이 기대하는 어​​떤 데이터 세트
not exactly what you might expect lots of cats is that the cat bias would be
정확히 당신이 고양이를 많이 기대하는 것은 고양이 바이어스가 될 것입니다
higher because this class this classifier is just used to large numbers
높은 때문에이 분류는 단지 큰 숫자에 사용되는이 클래스
based on the loss but we have to go into loss function to exactly see how that
손실에 기초하지만 우리는 볼을 정확하게에 손실 함수로 가야 어떻게
will play out so it's hard to say right now
그것은 지금 말할 하드 그래서 밖으로 재생됩니다
another interpretation of the classifier that also someone else pointed out that
또한 다른 사람이 지적 분류의 또 다른 해석
I'd like to point out is you can think of these images as very high-dimensional
내가 지적하고 싶은 당신은 매우 높은 차원으로 이러한 이미지 생각할 수있다
points in a 3072 dimensional space right into 3072 pixels space space every image
바로 3072 픽셀 공간 공간마다 이미지로 3072 차원 공간에서 점
is a point and these linear classifiers are describing these gradients across
점이며, 이러한 선형 분류 걸쳐 이러한 그라데이션을 설명하는
the three thousand something two dimensional space these scores are this
이 점수이있는 삼천 뭔가 2 차원
region and negative to positive along some liquor direction across the space
영역 및 공간에서 일부 주류 방향에 따른 긍정적 부정적
and so for example here for a classifier I'm taking the first row of W which is
그래서 여기에 예를 들어 분류에 대한 I는 W의 첫 번째 행을 데려 갈거야
the car class and to the line here is indicating the zero level set of the
자동차 클래스와 여기에 라인에가의 제로 레벨 세트를 표시한다
classifier in other words that long that line the car classifier has a zero score
자동차 분류 그 라인을 오랫동안 즉 분류가 0 점수가
so the car classifier there has 20 and then their arrows indicating the
그래서 차 분류기는 20을 표시하고 화살표가 그들의 갖는다
direction along which it will color the space with more and more
더 많은 공간으로 착색되는 방향을 따라
harness score similar we have three different classifiers in this example
우리는이 예에서 세 가지 분류가 점수 유사 활용
they will also respond to these gradients with particular level set and
특정 레벨 설정과 그들이 이러한 기울기에 반응하고
they're basically trying to go in if all these punks they are in the space and
그들은 기본적으로 그들은 공간에있는 모든 끼 경우에 이동하려는 및
these local suppliers we initialize then randomly saw this car classifier would
우리는 다음 초기화 이들 지역의 공급 업체가 임의로이 차 분류는 것 보았다
have its level set at random and then you'll see when we actually do the
그 수준이 무작위로 설정되어 우리가 실제로 작업을 수행 할 때 당신은 볼 수 있습니다
optimization as we optimize this will start your shift turn animal protein
우리가 최적화로 최적화이 당신의 시프트 차례 동물성 단백질을 시작합니다
isolate the car class and will like through fun to watch these classifiers
자동차 클래스를 분리하고이 분류를 보는 재미를 좋아합니다
trained because it will rotate will snap into the car crossing Dr Jekyll and will
이 박사 지킬과 의지를 건너 차에 스냅됩니다 회전하기 때문에 훈련
try to like separate out all the cars from all the upholding of course it's
그건 물론 모든 지키는에서 모든 차량을 분리하고자 시도
really amusing to watch so that's another way of interpreting that ok
보고 정말 재미 그래서 그 확인을 해석하는 또 다른 방법입니다
here's a question for you given all these interpretations would be a very
여기에 당신이 모든 해석은 매우 될 것 주어진에 대한 질문입니다
hard to such a pacifier works what would you expect to work really really not
이러한 젖꼭지 하드 당신이 정말로 정말로 일을 기대하는 것이 무엇 작동
well with a linear classifier
잘 선형 분류와
concurrent circle see our closest are your classes exactly how I see so you're
동시 원은 우리의 가장 가까운 참조 나는 그래서 당신이있어 볼 정확히 어떻게 수업은
in search of describing is in this interpretation of space in your images
설명을 찾아 이미지에 공간이 해석에
in one class would be in a blob and then your other classes like around it so I'm
하나의 클래스에 그렇게 난 주위에 같은 다른 클래스 다음 얼룩에와 것
not sure exactly what that would look like if you actually space but yes
즉, 예를 경우 실제로 공간 만 같을 것이다 정확하게 확실하지
you're right in that case clinic awesome I will not be able to separate out those
당신은 내가 그를 분리 할 수​​ 없습니다 굉장이 경우 병원에 맞아
but what about in terms of like what would the images look like you would
하지만 이미지는 것 당신처럼 대해 같은 측면에서 보일 것입니다 무슨
look at the studio setup images clearly say that later classifier will probably
스튜디오 설치 이미지를 보면 분명히 나중에 분류 아마 것이라고
not do very well here ya got
나중에있어 여기에 아주 잘하지
trained classifier and that I do a negative of it negative image of that
훈련을 분류하고 나는 그것을 그것의 부정적인 이미지를 부정 할 것을
classifier you still see the edges and you'll say okay that's an airplane
당신은 여전히​​ 가장자리를 참조 분류하고 괜찮 그 비행기 말할 수 있습니다
obviously by the shape battalion classifier all the colors would be
분명히 모양 대대 분류 모든 색상이 될 것이다
exactly wrong and so the cost I would hate that airplane
정확히 잘못 때문에 비용이 그 비행기를 싫어
example
예
dogs dogs dogs and one closest dogs in on the right and you think that would be
개는 개, 오른쪽에 하나의 가장 가까운 개를 개 및 해당 될 것이라고 생각
a problem right
문제의 권리
white background or something that would be a problem it wouldn't be a problem I
문제가 될 것입니다 흰색 배경이나 뭔가가 문제의 I되지 않을 것
wouldn't be a problem
문제가되지 않을 것입니다
transformation
변환
you're saying that may be more difficult thing would be if your dog that our work
당신이 더 어려울 수 있습니다 말하고있는 일이 될 것이다 당신의 개 우리의 작업을하는 경우
in some ways according to class why wouldn't it be a problem if you actually
어떤면에서는 클래스에 따라 왜 당신이 만약 실제로 문제가되지 않을 것입니다
do something in the center and something on the right doesn't actually have an
실제로이없는 오른쪽 중앙에 뭔가 일을
understanding up especially on that actually find right there would be a
그에 특히 최대 이해하는 것은 실제로 오른쪽이 될 것이다 발견
relatively easy because you would have positive weights in the middle
당신이 중간에 긍정적 인 가중치를해야하기 때문에 상대적으로 쉽게
ok
그래
yes so this is really really what it's doing here really what this is doing is
그것은 여기 정말이가 무엇을하고 있는지 무엇을하고 있는지 예 그래서 이것은 정말 정말
it's counting up coming up colors and special positions anything that messes
그것은 놨어요 색상 및 특수 위치 아무것도오고 카운트 업이야
with this will be really hard actually to go back to your point if you had a
이건 정말 힘들 것입니다 당신이 있던 경우에 실제로 지점으로 돌아갑니다
grayscale data set by the way that would work
작동하는 방법과 설정 그레이 스케일 데이터
not very well with our customers will probably not work if you could see far
아니 아주 잘 당신이 지금까지 볼 수 있다면 우리의 고객은 아마 작동하지 않습니다와 함께
10 and you made or grayscale then doing the exact same classification grayscale
10 당신은 제조 또는 그레이 스케일은 동일한 분류 그레이 스케일을 수행
images would probably work really terribly because you can't pick up on
당신이에서 선택할 수 없기 때문에 이미지는 아마 정말 끔찍하게 작동합니다
the colors you have to pick up on these textures and fine details now and you
색상은 이제 이러한 질감과 미세한 세부 사항을 데리러해야하고
just can't localize them because they could be very positions can't
그들이 할 수 있기 때문에 그냥 아주 위치가 없습니다를 지역화 할 수 없습니다
consistently come to cross it would be kind of a disaster
일관되게 재해의 종류 것 건너 와서
another example would be different textures if you have say all of your
당신이 모든 말을이있는 경우 또 다른 예는 서로 다른 질감을 것입니다 당신의
text are blue but these texts could be different types then this doesn't really
텍스트는 파란색하지만이 정말하지 않습니다이 텍스트는 다른 종류의 수
like say these two different types but they can be spatially invariant
같은 이러한 두 가지 유형의 말을하지만 그들은 공간적으로 불변 일 수있다
that would be terrible terrible get so just remind you I think nearly there
그, 그래서 그냥 내가 거의가 생각하는 당신을 생각 나게 얻을 끔찍한 끔찍한 것
would find this function so with specific case and W we're looking at
우리가보고있는 특정 케이스와 W에 있도록이 기능을 찾을 것입니다
some test images we're getting some scores out and just looking forward
몇 가지 테스트 이미지는 우리가 밖으로 약간의 점수를 받고 그냥 기대하고
we're headed now is with some setting up w for getting some scores for all these
우리는 지금 향하고 약간의 모든 일부 점수를 얻기 위해 w를 설정 함께있어
images and so for example with this setting up w in this image we're seeing
이미지 등이 이미지에서 우리가보고있는 w는이 설정을 위로 예를 들어,
that the cat score is 2.9 but there are some classes I've got a higher score
고양이 점수는 2.9하지만 나는 높은 점수있어 몇 가지 클래스가 있음
like dog so that's not very good right but some classes have negative scores
이들은 매우 좋은 권리는 아니지만 일부 클래스가 부정적인 점수를 그래서 개 같은
which is good for this image so this is kind of a medium result for this waits
이 종류의이 대기에 대한 중간 결과입니다 그래서이 이미지의 선한
for this image in here we see that the car class just correct for their has the
여기에서이 이미지를 우리는이 자신에 대한 그 차 클래스 단지 올바른 참조
highest score which is going to write so visiting W work too well on this image
이 이미지에 너무 잘 W 작업을 방문 그렇게 쓸 것입니다 가장 높은 점수
here we see that the class is a very low score so terribly on that so we're
여기에 우리는 클래스가 너무 끔찍 그에 우리가있어, 그래서 매우 낮은 점수 것을 볼
headed now is we're going to define what we call a loss function and this loss
지금 향했다 우리는 우리가 손실의 기능이 손실을 부르는 정의려고하고있다
function will quantify this intuition of what we considered good or bad right now
함수는 우리가 지금 좋은 또는 나쁜 생각 무엇을이 직관을 정량화한다
we're just eyeballing these numbers are saying what's good what's
우리가이 숫자를 째려하는 것은 무슨 무슨 좋은 말
which actually write down the mathematical expression that tells us
실제로 우리에게 수식을 기록하는
exactly like these setting up w across our test is 12.5 bad or 1220 whatever
바로 이러한 우리의 테스트에서 w를 설정처럼 나쁜 12.5 또는 1220 무엇이든
bad or 110 bad because then once we have a defined specifically we're going to be
우리가 구체적으로 정의한 후, 일단 우리가 될 것하고 있기 때문에 나쁜 또는 110 나쁜
looking forw that minimize the loss and it will be set up in such a way that
그 forw 찾고 손실을 최소화하고는 같은 방법으로 설정한다는
when you have a loss of very low numbers like say even zero and then your
다음도 제로 말처럼 당신은 매우 낮은 숫자의 손실이있을 때
correctly classifying all your images but if you have a very high loss then
정확하게 모든 이미지를 분류하지만 당신은 매우 높은 손실이있는 경우
everything is messed up in W is not good at all so we're going to find a lot of
모든 것이 W에 엉망이 전혀 우리가 많이 찾을거야 좋지 않다
action and then look for different w's that actually do very well across all of
실제로 모두에서 매우 잘 수행하는 것이 야 승 조치는 다음 다른 찾아
it so that's roughly what's coming up
그렇게 그 대략 무엇을오고있어
well-defined loss function which is a quantify a way to quantify how bad HW is
A는 정량화 방법이다 잘 정의 손실 함수는 HW가 얼마나 나쁜 정할
on our dataset the loss function as a function of your entire training set and
우리의 데이터 세트에 전체 학습 집합의 함수로 손실 함수와
your rates we don't have control over the transfer of control of weeds then
당신의 속도는 우리는 잡초 제어의 전송을 제어 할 수 없습니다
we're going to look at the process of optimization how to efficiently find the
우리는 어떻게 효율적를 찾기 위해 최적화하는 과정에서 볼거야
set of weights w that works across all of the images and gives us a very low
모든 이미지에서 작동 우리에게 매우 낮은을 제공합니다 가중치 w의 세트
loss and then eventually what we'll do is we'll go back and look at this
손실은 결국 우리가 무엇을 할 거 야 우리가 가서 이것 좀 봐 것입니다
expression classifier that we saw we're going to start meddling with the
우리가 보았던 식 분류 우리는 함께 간섭 시작하는거야
function here so we're going to expend effort to not be that simple your
여기에 기능 그래서 우리는 간단하지 노력을 소비거야 당신의
expression but we're going to make it slightly more complex will get a workout
표현하지만 우리는 조금 더 복잡한 운동을 얻을 수 있도록거야
and then we can slightly more complex and will get a coalition that work out
그리고, 우리는 조금 더 복잡하고 운동 연합을 얻을 수 있습니다
but otherwise the entire framework will stay unchanged all the time will be
하지만, 그 전체 프레임 워크는 모든 시간이 될 것입니다 변하지 남아있을 것입니다
competing these course dysfunctional formal be changing but we're going to
경쟁이 과정 역기능 형식이 변경 될 수 있지만, 우리는 거 야
some sort of course through some function and will make it more elaborate
어떤 종류의 코스 일부 기능을 통해 더 정교하게 만들 것
overtime and then we're identifying some loss function and we're looking at what
초과 근무 후 우리는 약간의 손실 함수를 식별하고 우리가보고있는 것을
waits what primaries are given a very low loss and that's a setup will be
예비 선거는 매우 낮은 손실을 부여하고이 설정이 될 것입니다 무엇을 기다립니다
working with going forward so next class will look into loss functions and then
다음 손실 기능에 모양 앞으로 그래서 다음 수업을가는 작업
we'll go to Arsenal Emirates income that's so I guess this is my last light
우리는 그래서 이것이 나의 마지막 빛 추측있어 그 아스날 에미리트 소득에 갈거야
so I can take up any last questions and
그래서 어떤 마지막 질문에 걸릴 수 있고,
sorry sorry sorry I didn't hear
죄송합니다 죄송합니다 죄송합니다 나는 듣지 않았다
the project optimization are sometimes in opposition settings you can operate
프로젝트 최적화 야당 설정하면 작동 할 수 있습니다에 때때로
these innovative approaches are basically the way this will work we'll
이러한 혁신적인 접근은 기본적으로이 거 우리를 작동 방법입니다
see we'll always start off with the random W so that will give us some loss
우리는 항상 랜덤 W로 시작합니다 참조하면 그것은 우리에게 손실을 줄 것이다 있도록
and then we we don't have a process of finding right away the best set of
그리고, 우리 우리의 바로 최고의 세트를 찾는 과정이 없습니다
weights but we do have a process for is iteratively slightly improving the
무게는하지만 우리는 반복적으로 약간을 개선하는 방법을해야합니까
weights so little see as we look at the loss function and will find a gradient
무게가 너무 작은 우리가 손실 함수에서 보면보고 ​​그라데이션을 찾을 수
and space and will march down so what we do know how to do is how do we slightly
공간과 우리가하는 방법을 알고 무엇을 약간 우리를 어떻게되어 아래로 행진한다
improved a set of weights we don't know how to do the problem of just buying the
우리가 단지 구입의 문제를 수행하는 방법을 모르는 가중치의 세트를 향상
best way through right away we don't know how to do that because especially
바로 통해 가장 좋은 방법은 우리가 그렇게하는 방법을 모르겠어요 특히 때문에
when these functions are very complex likes a intercom that's a huge landscape
이러한 기능은 매우 복잡 할 때 거대한 풍경의 인터콤을 좋아한다
of its just a very intractable problem is that your question I'm not sure how
그 단지 매우 다루기 힘든 문제 귀하의 질문에 내가 어떻게 잘 모르겠어요 것입니다
do we deal with the color problem so ok so so here we saw that the linear
우리가 여기에 너무 너무 좋아 색상 문제를 처리 할 우리는 선형 것을보고
classifier for car was this red template for a car and neural network basically
자동차에 대한 분류는 기본적으로 자동차와 신경망이 빨간색 템플릿했다
what we'll do is we'll meet will you can look at it as stacking when you're
우리가 할 거 야 우리가 당신이있을 때 당신이 적층로 볼 수 있습니다 것 만날입니다
classifier to some degree so what it will end up doing is it will have all
어느 정도 분류 그래서 그것이 모든 것입니다 일을 결국 무슨
these little templates really for rent cars cars cars cars going this way or
이 길을가는 정말 임대 자동차 자동차 자동차 자동차에 대한이 작은 템플릿 또는
that way or that way there will be assigned to the technique every one of
그 방법 또는 그 방법으로는 기술에 할당됩니다 거기에 모든 사람의
these different modes and then they will be combined across them on the second
이러한 다양한 모드는 다음 그들은 두 번째에 그에서 결합됩니다
layer so basically you have these are looking for different types of course
이러한 서로 다른 종류의 코스를 찾고있다 그래서 기본적 층
and then next year on will be just like ok I just take a way to tell if you guys
다음에 내년 난 그냥 경우를 말할 수있는 방법을 바로 확인처럼 될 것입니다 너희들
are doing or operation over you and then we can detect cars in all of their modes
일이나 이상 동작, 그리고, 우리는 모든 모드에서 차를 검출 할 수있다
of their positions that makes sense that's roughly homework
자신의 위치의 대략 숙제의 의미가 있습니다